<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
<sample number="1">He performed at the Habitat Center, New Delhi on a visit to <loc reading="lit">India</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="2">Zalog is a formerly independent settlement in the eastern part of the capital <loc reading="lit">Ljubljana</loc> in central Slovenia.
</sample>
<sample number="3"><loc reading="lit">Beacon Hill</loc> is a neighbourhood located in Beacon Hill-Cyrville Ward in the east end of Ottawa, Ontario, Canada.
</sample>
<sample number="4">This marine species occurs in the Indian Ocean (Tanzania, <loc reading="lit">Mascarene Islands</loc>) and eastwards as far as Indonesia.
</sample>
<sample number="5">There is no road connection to the rest of <loc reading="lit">Norway</loc>, even though it is located on the mainland.
</sample>
<sample number="6"><loc reading="lit">Cambodia</loc> is a country located in South East Asia that has a major problem with landmines, especially in rural areas.
</sample>
<sample number="7">After <loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> won the playoff and gained qualification, Herrera's job was extended to coaching the team during the World Cup.
</sample>
<sample number="8">Her parents, Matthew and Julia Moore, had come to the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> in 1888 and were living at 32 Monroe Street in Manhattan.
</sample>
<sample number="9">However, the conditions of the post-war world encouraged decolonialization and emergence of new governments, with India, <loc reading="met">Pakistan</loc>, Israel, Vietnam, and others declaring independence, although rarely without bloodshed.
</sample>
<sample number="10"><loc reading="lit">Suriname</loc>'s low population density and abundant natural resources have attracted numerous migrants from neighboring Brazil.
</sample>
<sample number="11">He began his career at Monagas, playing four Primera División Venezolana seasons before a transfer to <loc reading="met">Caracas</loc> in 2012.
</sample>
<sample number="12">Pointe Coupee Parish School Board is a school district headquartered in unincorporated <loc reading="lit">Pointe Coupee Parish</loc>, Louisiana, United States.
</sample>
<sample number="13">The descriptions of M. slaina ants were based on worker, queen and males collected from various places in Siberia and <loc reading="lit">Kazakhstan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="14">The group was presented to the Prince of Wales, later King Charles I, in 1623 while he was in <loc reading="lit">Spain</loc> negotiating a marriage contract, and it soon became the most famous Italian sculpture in England.
</sample>
<sample number="15"><loc reading="met">China</loc> estimated in 2009 that 3,000 of the Chinese in Romania consisted of migrant workers, in the textile, shipbuilding, construction, and agriculture sectors.
</sample>
<sample number="16">And there's no such case - they were all Serbs before, and did not belong to one of the peoples of <loc reading="lit">Montenegro</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="17">Donald Lu is currently the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> ambassador.
</sample>
<sample number="18">Important themes include the rapid industrialization and growing power of Britain, Europe and, later in the period, the United States, with <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> emerging as a major power and empire towards the end of this period.
</sample>
<sample number="19">The English side had lost the previous tour to <loc reading="met">Australia</loc>, but had remained undefeated at home by visiting Australian sides.
</sample>
<sample number="20"><loc reading="met">Ukraine</loc>, similarly to most other developing countries, suffers from ineffectiveness and corruption in public services sphere.
</sample>
<sample number="21"><loc reading="met">Canada</loc> and the USA joined the nine teams that played in the 1978 European Curling Championships.
</sample>
<sample number="22">She served in the Mediterranean and then participated in the war against <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> with the British Eastern Fleet.
</sample>
<sample number="23">The 1965 Los Angeles Dodgers finished the regular-season with a 97–65 record, which earned them the NL pennant by two games over their arch-rivals, <loc reading="met">San Francisco</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="24">He spoke about the need to change the terms of trade between industrialized countries and developing countries, and affirmed the will of <loc reading="met">France</loc> to actively contribute to the development of the Third World.
</sample>
<sample number="25">Lyse Abbey was founded in 1146 by Sigurd, Bishop of Bergen, on farmland that he owned, as the Christianisation of <loc reading="met">Norway</loc> was nearing completion.
</sample>
<sample number="26">When his father died two years later, his mother moved to Buenos Aires, establishing in <loc reading="lit">Balvanera</loc> district.
</sample>
<sample number="27">He helped the Reggae Boyz to capture the 2014 CFU Caribbean Football Unions (men's) Title beating <loc reading="met">Trinidad and Tobago</loc> in Penalties.
</sample>
<sample number="28">The album was then given a final remix in the <loc reading="lit">UK</loc> by producer John Brand.
</sample>
<sample number="29">The 2012 Community Shield was broadcast live in the <loc reading="lit">United Kingdom</loc> on ITV1.
</sample>
<sample number="30">Returning to Bulgaria as volunteers in the Balkan Wars of 1912 and 1913, they brought back the new music of <loc reading="met">America</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="31">Once the abbot went to <loc reading="lit">Italy</loc>, the four brothers decided to celebrate, yet they needed some money.
</sample>
<sample number="32">In July 1941, after the Nazi Germany attacked the <loc reading="met">Soviet Union</loc>, Buczacz was taken over by the Germans.
</sample>
<sample number="33">This meant a factory could be set up anywhere in <loc reading="lit">India</loc> and the transportation of minerals would be subsidised by the central government.
</sample>
<sample number="34">After independence of <loc reading="met">India</loc>, he represented Kutch constituency in 3rd Lok Sabha, for the years 1962–67, as a member of Swatantra Party which won over the rival Congress party.
</sample>
<sample number="35">Linux Foundation started organizing similar events in Europe and <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="36">"Waters &amp; Watson" itself was established in 1933 but ceased operations when <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> invaded Singapore in 1942.
</sample>
<sample number="37">Airport City Accra is an urban development within the Airport enclave of <loc reading="lit">Accra</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="38">"During a night meeting with Adolf Hitler and Hermann Göring in Berlin on between 14 and 15 of March, 1939 he was threatened with aerial bombardment of <loc reading="lit">Prague</loc> and forced to sign a document accepting of incorporation of Bohemia and Moravia into Germany even though he did not consult the parliament beforehand."
</sample>
<sample number="39">Billy Murdoch won the toss for <loc reading="met">Australia</loc> and chose to bat first.
</sample>
<sample number="40">The West London Derby is the name given to a football derby played between any two of Brentford, Chelsea, <loc reading="met">Fulham</loc> and Queens Park Rangers, all of whom are situated within West or Southwest London.
</sample>
<sample number="41"><loc reading="met">Philippines</loc> participated in the 2010 Asian Para Games–First Asian Para Games in Guangzhou, China from 13 to 19 December 2010.
</sample>
<sample number="42">Holy Saviour's Cathedral is a former Anglican cathedral in Xicheng District of Beijing, <loc reading="lit">China</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="43"><loc reading="lit">Koepenick</loc> is an unincorporated community located in the town of Upham, Langlade County, Wisconsin, United States.
</sample>
<sample number="44">He lived for most of the last decade of his life in London and frequently travelled between Europe and <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="45">At the graduation of the Academy, in 2010, Ekaterine Chitashvili moved to <loc reading="lit">Moldova</loc> and was the general company producer Elat Concerts, she was engaged in conducting international music festivals and competitions, television, music projects and producing popular talented bands and moldavian artists.But the main activity for Ekaterine was to enlarge the contacts and affiliates own international concert of MaximuM, a company that today has 13 offices in the Americas, Europe and CIS.
</sample>
<sample number="46">The conference ended with the <loc reading="met">Netherlands</loc> agreeing to transfer sovereignty to the United States of Indonesia.
</sample>
<sample number="47">He finished only in fortieth place by one point behind <loc reading="lit">New Zealand</loc>'s Yang Wang from the fourth attempt, for a total score of 571 targets.
</sample>
<sample number="48"><loc reading="met">Russia</loc> is sole successor to the Soviet Union, so ties have naturally continued with Russia since the Belavezha Accords.
</sample>
<sample number="49"><loc reading="met">Australia</loc> batted first and scored 240 runs for 9 wickets in 50 overs.
</sample>
<sample number="50">The Cat Island, part of the Babel Group within the Furneaux Group, is a 39-hectare (96-acre) unpopulated granite island, located in Bass Strait, lying off the east coast of Flinders Island, <loc reading="lit">Tasmania</loc>, south of Victoria, in south-eastern Australia.
</sample>
<sample number="51">At the time of Federation the very few people who lived in the Northern Territory voted as residents of <loc reading="lit">South Australia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="52"><loc reading="met">Argentina</loc> returned to the WRC calendar for the first time since 2009, after the event was a part of the Intercontinental Rally Challenge in 2010.
</sample>
<sample number="53">The ship was to be built in <loc reading="lit">China</loc> and set sail in late 2016, later postponed to 2018.
</sample>
<sample number="54"><loc reading="met">Spain</loc> was led in scoring in the 2012 Gold Coast Sevens by Pedro Martin (5 tries and 27 points), and by Pablo Feijoo (4 tries and 22 points).
</sample>
<sample number="55">Laksono is known for his brash condescendence and overtly harsh remarks towards <loc reading="met">Singapore</loc>, especially with regards to the island republic's diplomatic calls to the Indonesian government to curb the acrid trans-boundary haze that shrouds large areas of Sumatra, Peninsular Malaysia and Singapore annually as a result of extensive "slash and burn" cultivation in Sumatra, Kalimantan and other Indonesian territories.
</sample>
<sample number="56">The township comprises the communities of Beamsville, Campden, <loc reading="lit">Jordan</loc>, Jordan Station, Pelham Union, Rockway, Tintern, Vineland and Vineland Station.
</sample>
<sample number="57">During the 1980s, the <loc reading="met">Soviet Union</loc> provided full political, economic, military, and diplomatic support to the left wing government of Nicaragua.
</sample>
<sample number="58">The alleged causes were the centralistic policies of the Maldivian government and the recent independence of its neighbors <loc reading="met">India</loc> and Ceylon.
</sample>
<sample number="59">The Salar de Olaroz is a salt lake in the province of Jujuy in northwestern Argentina, close to the <loc reading="lit">Chile</loc> border.
</sample>
<sample number="60">Lebedeva competed in the 2010 Winter Olympics for <loc reading="met">Kazakhstan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="61">The United States Ambassador to Albania is the head of the diplomatic mission of the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> to Albania.
</sample>
<sample number="62">Important themes include the rapid industrialization and growing power of <loc reading="met">Britain</loc>, Europe and, later in the period, the United States, with Japan emerging as a major power and empire towards the end of this period.
</sample>
<sample number="63">Today, it is almost nonexistent in <loc reading="lit">France</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="64"><loc reading="met">Germany</loc> attacks the Soviet Union (June 22, 1941).
</sample>
<sample number="65">Echoing the Taif Agreement, the resolution "calls upon all remaining foreign forces to withdraw from <loc reading="lit">Lebanon</loc>" and "for the disbanding and disarmament of all Lebanese and non-Lebanese militias."
</sample>
<sample number="66">He started in <loc reading="met">India</loc>'s only match that tournament against Yugoslavia on 15 July 1952.
</sample>
<sample number="67">From the seventies onward, Novarro lived part of the time in <loc reading="lit">Germany</loc>, because he considered Europe "the center of art".
</sample>
<sample number="68">In 2003 he was awarded <loc reading="lit">New Zealand</loc>'s coach of the year and was nominated again in 2005.
</sample>
<sample number="69">The United States and France both formally recognized <loc reading="met">Algeria</loc> on that same day.
</sample>
<sample number="70">Published in <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> between 1923 and 1978 with no notice of copyright in original publication, public domain.
</sample>
<sample number="71">The year 2007 is the 11th year in the history of the Pride Fighting Championships, a mixed martial arts promotion based in <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="72">In 1793, Brunel had to flee the revolution, going to the United States, but Sophia remained in <loc reading="lit">Rouen</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="73">He played for Ellerslie and <loc reading="met">Wellington</loc> during the 80's but injury curtailed his playing career as a goalkeeper.
</sample>
<sample number="74">S. antipodes is endemic to the waters off eastern Australia and <loc reading="lit">Tasmania</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="75">Kim competed at the 2014 Winter Olympics for <loc reading="met">South Korea</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="76">On September 29, 1962, diplomatic relations between <loc reading="met">Algeria</loc> and the United States were formally established when the U.S. Consulate General in Algiers was raised to embassy status.
</sample>
<sample number="77">During consideration of Dickerson v. <loc reading="met">United States</loc>, BLAG submitted an amicus brief to the Fourth Circuit.
</sample>
<sample number="78">The concept of two newspapers in one Redaktion was then new for <loc reading="met">Germany</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="79">Additionally, <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>'s population is highly concentrated in coastal areas, and its important tourism industry depends on the health of the Great Barrier Reef and other fragile ecosystems.
</sample>
<sample number="80"><loc reading="met">Australia</loc> were criticised by the Indian media for pushing the President of Board of Control for Cricket in India (BCCI) and Minister in the Government of India, Sharad Pawar, off the dais.
</sample>
<sample number="81">Most were selected from shrines that were in the immediate vicinity of <loc reading="lit">Kyoto</loc>, the capital of Japan at the time.
</sample>
<sample number="82"><loc reading="lit">Italy</loc>'s architecture almost spans 3,000 years, and has renowned differences in style: from Etruscan and ancient Roman style buildings, to Romanesque, Gothic, Renaissance, Baroque, Rococo, Neoclassical, Empire style, Art Nouveau, Fascism and modern architecture.
</sample>
<sample number="83">Borislav Pekić spent his childhood in different cities of Serbia, Montenegro and <loc reading="lit">Croatia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="84">And, of course, the Avila daughter, <loc reading="met">Sofia</loc> has invited her non-Latino boyfriend.
</sample>
<sample number="85">Newman won the Congressional Gold Medal awarded by the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> for his flight in the Double Eagle II with Ben Abruzzo and Maxie Anderson.
</sample>
<sample number="86">The cooperation between these two nations on an issue concerning the <loc reading="met">Middle East</loc> was seen as a significant improvement in their relationship, compared to their earlier bitter disagreement over the 2003 invasion of Iraq.
</sample>
<sample number="87">On 5 January 2016, Panetolikos announced that Bejarano would be returning to <loc reading="lit">Bolivia</loc> for six months to play for Club Bolívar.
</sample>
<sample number="88">Assa Hougoud is a city in central <loc reading="lit">Djibouti</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="89">As of 2000 <loc reading="met">Ghana</loc>’s main exports were minerals and cocoa.
</sample>
<sample number="90">Although her film career didn't take off until she was well into her forties, she is regarded as one of <loc reading="lit">China</loc>'s most talented female directors.
</sample>
<sample number="91">For the first time since 1998 the <loc reading="met">Netherlands</loc>' song was performed in Dutch.
</sample>
<sample number="92">Back in <loc reading="lit">Spain</loc>, he served as fiscal of Burgos and as official in the provinces of Navarra, Guipúzcoa and Zaragoza.
</sample>
<sample number="93">It has an estimated population of 176,030 in 2014, and the capital and largest city of the state is <loc reading="lit">Terekeka</loc>, South Sudan.
</sample>
<sample number="94">Gender reassignment surgery has been practised since the 1930s, and available in the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> from 1965.
</sample>
<sample number="95">In 1977-78 season, he helped <loc reading="met">South China</loc> to create the record of unbeaten in Hong Kong First Division League for the season.
</sample>
<sample number="96">He became chancellor of <loc reading="lit">Sicily</loc> in 1343 and legate of Pope Innocent VI in Dauphiné in 1353 and in Germany in 1358.
</sample>
<sample number="97">During the occupation of Norway by <loc reading="met">Germany</loc> he was imprisoned in Grini concentration camp from 13 to 21 January 1942.
</sample>
<sample number="98">In the mid to late-1930's with the Spanish Civil War and the blackshirts of Oswald Mosley marching through the Jewish getto of the east end of <loc reading="lit">London</loc>, Nat and many of his contemporaries chose to join the British Army.
</sample>
<sample number="99">It is one of the top booking stations in <loc reading="lit">India</loc> according to Indian Railways.
</sample>
<sample number="100">In November a poll conducted by private broadcaster RTL 4 revealed that 86% of those polled would agree to a possible withdraw by the <loc reading="met">Netherlands</loc> due to the poor results received in past contests.
</sample>
<sample number="101">She was the first immigrant to the United States to pass through the <loc reading="lit">Ellis Island</loc> facility in New York Harbor.
</sample>
<sample number="102">Badaracchi represented <loc reading="met">Italy</loc> at the 2008 Summer Olympics in Beijing, where he competed in the men's 10 m air pistol, along with his teammate Vigilio Fait.
</sample>
<sample number="103">It called upon <loc reading="met">Lebanon</loc> to establish its sovereignty over all of its land and called upon "foreign forces" (Israel and Syria) to withdraw from Lebanon and to cease intervening in the internal politics of Lebanon.
</sample>
<sample number="104">He won a gold medal in the individual sprint event at the 1948 Summer Olympics in <loc reading="lit">London</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="105">Galantiči is a small settlement south of Kubed in the City Municipality of <loc reading="lit">Koper</loc> in the Littoral region of Slovenia.
</sample>
<sample number="106"><loc reading="met">Turkey</loc> participated at the 2010 Winter Olympics in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada.
</sample>
<sample number="107">The <loc reading="met">Kingdom of Poland</loc> was created out of the Duchy of Warsaw, a French client state, at the Congress of Vienna in 1815 when the great powers reorganized Europe following the Napoleonic wars.
</sample>
<sample number="108">The Algerian government had recognized the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> in 1795, but formal diplomatic relations had not been established.
</sample>
<sample number="109">In the beginning, Horus the falcon god of light and Set the god of evil fought to control <loc reading="met">Egypt</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="110">Marcelle Auclair was born 11 November 1899 in Montluçon, central <loc reading="lit">France</loc>, and died in Paris on 6 June 1984.
</sample>
<sample number="111">For a while the Squadron operated a detached flight at RAF Wick running a regular service to <loc reading="lit">Reykjavík</loc> in Iceland using de Havilland DH.91 Albatross aircraft, but when both were lost this was abandoned, the detached flight instead acquiring de Havilland Dominies, which were used to supply remote Scottish communities.
</sample>
<sample number="112">This result qualified him to the 2010 Summer Youth Olympics in <loc reading="lit">Singapore</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="113">It was mapped from surveys by the <loc reading="met">Falkland Islands</loc>, and was named by the UK Antarctic Place-Names Committee after the Eliason motor sledge, invented in 1942 in Sweden, now made in Canada, and used in Arctic Canada since 1950 and in the Antarctic since 1960.
</sample>
<sample number="114">Civita di Bagnoregio is a town in the Province of Viterbo in central Italy, a suburb of the comune of <loc reading="lit">Bagnoregio</loc>, 1 kilometre (0.6 miles) east from it.
</sample>
<sample number="115">This makes it the top free-to-air television program on Saturday evening, and it's also the most viewed non-drama program in <loc reading="lit">South Korea</loc> every week (excluding special sporting events, since November 2006, with the exception of January 2009, April and May 2010).
</sample>
<sample number="116">He began his musical studies in his country (Venezuela) and continued in Germany and <loc reading="lit">Poland</loc>, at the European Mozart Academy.
</sample>
<sample number="117">In the case of <loc reading="lit">Paris</loc>, the urban area is divided in about 420 different munipalities (nearly as many as in the whole Belgium).
</sample>
<sample number="118"><loc reading="met">Thailand</loc> does the same, and also in Norway it is illegal to sell alcohol on election day.
</sample>
<sample number="119">In <loc reading="lit">Greece</loc> and Cyprus, sesame seed candy is called pasteli and is generally a flat, oblong bar made with honey and often including nuts.
</sample>
<sample number="120">Since then Bayik has been a political leader in the PKK and is in charge of the organisation's relations with <loc reading="met">Iran</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="121">The bridge carries the <loc reading="lit">Waterloo</loc> to Reading Line and all trains serving its spur, the Weybridge or Chertsey Branch which connects this line to the four-track South Western Main Line running from London Waterloo to the far south-west, merging with the Devon and Cornwall main line.
</sample>
<sample number="122"><loc reading="lit">Howe</loc> is an unincorporated community in Nemaha County, Nebraska, in the United States.
</sample>
<sample number="123">Initially the school was established to provide a British style education for the children of expatriates working in <loc reading="lit">Seychelles</loc> on temporary contract.
</sample>
<sample number="124">Honoré took the title of Prince himself, and it was only through the protection of <loc reading="met">France</loc> that Monaco escaped total overrun by Spain.
</sample>
<sample number="125"><loc reading="met">Russia</loc> has an embassy in Managua.
</sample>
<sample number="126">The Bombay Hook Lighthouse (also called the Smyrna River Lighthouse) was built by the <loc reading="met">US</loc> in 1831.
</sample>
<sample number="127"><loc reading="met">South Africa</loc> scored 258 runs for eight wickets in 50 overs with Herschelle Gibbs scoring 77 runs.
</sample>
<sample number="128">There is conflicting data about whether or not <loc reading="met">Morocco</loc> competed in Mexico summer games in 1968.
</sample>
<sample number="129">After graduation from the National Theatre School, he and his wife spent a year interning with theatre companies in both Northern Ireland and the <loc reading="lit">Republic of Ireland</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="130">The Championship was won by Switzerland, who beat <loc reading="met">Sweden</loc> 13-5 in the final.
</sample>
<sample number="131">Prior to this conference, three other high-level meetings between the Netherlands and <loc reading="met">Indonesia</loc> took place.
</sample>
<sample number="132">Acacia flexifolia, commonly known as bent-leaf wattle, is a shrub species that is endemic to eastern <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="133"><loc reading="lit">Syria</loc> remained the Umayyads' main power base thereafter, and Damascus was their capital.
</sample>
<sample number="134">Most Southern African import and export commodities are handled through <loc reading="lit">South Africa</loc>'s six largest ports: Richards Bay, Durban, Saldanha, Cape Town, Port Elizabeth and East London.
</sample>
<sample number="135">LCI remained in the South Pacific until <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> capitulated.
</sample>
<sample number="136">At first, the twinned models were assembled by Ford in the <loc reading="lit">US</loc> for North American consumption, with Mazda in Japan supplying cars for other markets.
</sample>
<sample number="137"><loc reading="met">Montpellier</loc>'s other honours to date include winning the Coupe de France in 1929 and 1990, and the UEFA Intertoto Cup in 1999.
</sample>
<sample number="138">Mathews won some support for his studies outside <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="139">It originated from Uruguay and <loc reading="lit">Argentina</loc> in the mid-1940s, with apparent characteristics of simplicity and implications that are often unforeseeable and absolutely involving.
</sample>
<sample number="140">José Francisco Razzano born in Montevideo, near <loc reading="lit">Plaza Independencia</loc>, on February 25, 1887.
</sample>
<sample number="141">Based in <loc reading="lit">Beirut</loc>, Lebanon 1964-66, he published photographs and articles on subjects such as the Kurds of Iraq in Life, the Sunday Times, Geographical Magazine and others.
</sample>
<sample number="142">Franco Forini (born 22 September 1958 in Muralto) is a former racing driver from <loc reading="lit">Switzerland</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="143">If you oppose <loc reading="met">Russia</loc>, please find a way to do so which does not affect the work of Wikipedia users.
</sample>
<sample number="144">This is awarded to the player of the tournament and is named in honour of the <loc reading="met">New Zealand</loc> forward who scored the winning try for the All Golds in the last minutes of the game to secure an 8 - 5 victory.
</sample>
<sample number="145">It is the third highest peak in <loc reading="lit">Romania</loc> after Moldoveanu Peak (2544m) and Negoiu Peak (2535m).
</sample>
<sample number="146">MiniDisc was announced by Sony in September 1992 and released that November for sale in <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc> and in December in Europe, Canada, the USA and other countries.
</sample>
<sample number="147">By 1916, it was the largest oil company in <loc reading="lit">Russia</loc>, producing 76 million poods of oil.
</sample>
<sample number="148">He also won the team championship in 1939 in <loc reading="lit">Cairo</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="149">In September 2008, perhaps in response to <loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc>'s support over the breakaway Georgian territories, Russia offered to strengthen ties with Nicaragua and to provide aid to Nicaragua to help rebuild areas damaged by hurricanes.
</sample>
<sample number="150">But nobody knows even the approximate period of the finalization of these triple-points, because it needs the consent of <loc reading="met">India</loc> indeed, as an inevitable fact.
</sample>
<sample number="151">In May 1979, Mexico broke diplomatic relations with <loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc> over repeated human rights abuses carried out by the government of Anastasio Somoza Debayle.
</sample>
<sample number="152">Measuring almost four meters in width, Ecclesia militans is one of the largest icons ever produced in medieval <loc reading="lit">Russia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="153">William Nessen, an American freelance journalist, travels to <loc reading="lit">Aceh</loc>, Indonesia to cover the conflict which was taking place there at the time.
</sample>
<sample number="154">The first crowned Holy Roman Empress since the mid-15th century, she was responsible from the moving of the Imperial court from Prague to <loc reading="lit">Vienna</loc>, which became one of the centers of European culture.
</sample>
<sample number="155">In 1995, Smith wrote another book about <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc> and the Bulls, called Second Coming: The Strange Odyssey of Michael Jordan - From Courtside to Home Plate and Back Again.
</sample>
<sample number="156">Overall, he has totalled over 50 goals and over 150 appearances in the league, and made his international debut for <loc reading="met">Venezuela</loc> in 2010.
</sample>
<sample number="157">Armando Costa, also known as Rilhas, was born in 1949 in the village of <loc reading="lit">Bombarral</loc> in central Portugal.
</sample>
<sample number="158">Côte d'Ivoire, <loc reading="met">Ghana</loc> and Niger qualify for the final tournament.
</sample>
<sample number="159">His father, John Bird was a <loc reading="lit">London</loc> goldsmith with ancestral roots in Cheshire, England.
</sample>
<sample number="160"><loc reading="met">Panama</loc> is competing at the 2013 World Aquatics Championships in Barcelona, Spain between 19 July and 4 August 2013.
</sample>
<sample number="161">In the late 19th century, the newly united <loc reading="met">Italy</loc> was added to this group.
</sample>
<sample number="162">At least in 961, when King Otto I of Germany marched against the <loc reading="met">Kingdom of Italy</loc> for the second time, he made Hermann the administrator (procurator regis) in his Saxon lands.
</sample>
<sample number="163">She was one of the first locomotives to be built in <loc reading="lit">Germany</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="164">After he had finished his secondary edition he immigrated to <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> where he stayed until 1969.
</sample>
<sample number="165">Since independence on August 1, 1960, <loc reading="met">Benin</loc> has provided a model of democracy in West Africa.
</sample>
<sample number="166">At the time of the 1991 <loc reading="lit">Nepal</loc> census it had a population of 2,891 and had 530 houses in the village.
</sample>
<sample number="167">The line was first authorised in 1866, and was a proposed single line to connect <loc reading="lit">Soho</loc> on the Great Western Railway Birmingham to Wolverhampton route with Lapal, on a proposed line from Halesowen to Bromsgrove, with a connection to the London and North Western Railway (LNWR) near Monument Lane.
</sample>
<sample number="168">He was educated at Emanuel School in Battersea, London and rowed for GB at U23 Level and for <loc reading="met">Wales</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="169">Israel has its own Afganistan which is Syria, and its own Iraq, which is <loc reading="met">Iran</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="170">Corbin has represented <loc reading="met">Barbados</loc> in eleven Chess Olympiads from 1986 through 2008, playing first board in 1986, 1990, 1998, and 2000.
</sample>
<sample number="171">Amalia wrote a song book which is currently found in the German national library in Berlin, with copies in the public library of <loc reading="lit">Frankfurt</loc> and the university library of Frankfurt.
</sample>
<sample number="172">After primary, Lesedi then went to Wendywood high school in Sandton, <loc reading="lit">Gauteng</loc>, South Africa then later completing his matriculation at Lighthouse Christian College Brits North West, South Africa..
</sample>
<sample number="173">Its fake covers of prominent newspaper were sensational media pranks; the authors even distributed a fake Pravda in <loc reading="lit">Russia</loc> during communist rule.
</sample>
<sample number="174">Ignacio "Tiki" Inchausti played in <loc reading="met">Spain</loc>'s only ever appearance at.
</sample>
<sample number="175">Born in Wrentham, Suffolk, the son of Reverend Andrew Ritchie, he was educated at University College, <loc reading="lit">London</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="176">Traveling to <loc reading="lit">Rome</loc> in 1619, he also would have been exposed to the influence of Caravaggio and his followers.
</sample>
<sample number="177">He served in the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> military during the Korean War.
</sample>
<sample number="178"><loc reading="met">Mongolia</loc> finished nineteenth in a medal table.
</sample>
<sample number="179">This marine species occurs in the Caribbean Sea off <loc reading="lit">Colombia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="180">Their self-titled debut album made a strong impression in the <loc reading="lit">UK</loc>, as well as in Australia and New Zealand.
</sample>
<sample number="181">So the gods chose Papyrus, a young fisherman who must find the secret entrance to Ombos, free the god Horus and restore peace to <loc reading="met">Egypt</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="182">Set against the backdrop of the Indian Emergency, the movie tells the story of three youngsters in the 1970s, when <loc reading="met">India</loc> was undergoing massive social and political changes.
</sample>
<sample number="183">After having passed the summer of 2005 between Italy and <loc reading="met">Switzerland</loc> with the Favola tour.
</sample>
<sample number="184">The <loc reading="met">Pakistan</loc> conducted armed operations against these Al-Qaeda members since August 2003 off and on with limited success.
</sample>
<sample number="185">Harvard School (pre Harvard-Westlake) was named after John Harvard of Southwick, borough of <loc reading="lit">London</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="186">She received awards in recognition of her humanitarian work from the governments of such nations as Belgium, Czechoslovakia, Estonia, <loc reading="met">Japan</loc>, Latvia, Lithuania, Romania, as well as Imperial Russia.
</sample>
<sample number="187">Detremmerie was born in Mouscron, traditionally a French speaking textile manufacturing town sandwiched between the frontier with <loc reading="lit">France</loc> to the south, and the Dutch language frontier to the north, in the western part of occupied Belgium.
</sample>
<sample number="188">Since the 1980s China as well as <loc reading="met">Thailand</loc> have farmed tigers with the idea of selling their parts to meet the demand for tiger bone .
</sample>
<sample number="189">Hope For The Warriors is a national nonprofit organization in the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> that provides assistance to combat wounded service members, their families, and families of those killed in action.
</sample>
<sample number="190">In 1978 it began to be marketed in <loc reading="lit">France</loc> for patients at high risk for thrombotic events: postoperative cardiac patients, patients undergoing hemodialysis, peripheral vascular disease, and the prevention of strokes and ischemic heart disease.
</sample>
<sample number="191">During his reign <loc reading="met">Polotsk</loc> was at war with Kiev and Novgorod.
</sample>
<sample number="192">Born in Australia in November 1956, Delacy has been part of the <loc reading="lit">Hong Kong</loc> broadcasting industry since 1979.
</sample>
<sample number="193"><loc reading="met">Bolivia</loc> held a parliamentary election on 1 May 1927, electing a new National Congress.
</sample>
<sample number="194">The Grand National Party of President Lee Myung-bak won a majority of seats in the National Assembly of <loc reading="lit">South Korea</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="195">After Sandinista leader Daniel Ortega returned to power in 2007, <loc reading="met">Russia</loc> took over the patron role for Nicaragua Nicaragua was the second country after Russia to recognize the disputed territories of South Ossetia and Abkhazia.
</sample>
<sample number="196">Before the Syrian war, <loc reading="lit">Homs</loc> was a major industrial centre, and with a population of at least 652,609 people in 2004, it was the third largest city in Syria after Aleppo to the north and the capital Damascus to the south.
</sample>
<sample number="197">Same-sex sexual acts are illegal in <loc reading="lit">Antigua</loc> and Barbuda.
</sample>
<sample number="198">Kerala Iyers, like the Iyers of Tamil Nadu and the Nambudiris of Kerala, belonged to the Pancha-Dravida classification of <loc reading="lit">India</loc>'s Brahmin community.
</sample>
<sample number="199"><loc reading="met">Dublin</loc> provided the opposition on that occasion, however, victory went to Galway and Clarke collected a coveted All-Ireland medal.
</sample>
<sample number="200">New York State Route 50 (NY 50) is a 31.67-mile (50.97 km) state highway in the Capital District of New York in the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="201">Stephen Parke (born 1950) is a <loc reading="lit">New Zealand</loc> physicist.
</sample>
<sample number="202">Once <loc reading="met">Italy</loc> entered the war in 1915, Balbo joined the Italian Royal Army (Regio Esercito) as an officer candidate and served in the Alpini (Mountain) Battalion "Val Fella" before volunteering for flying training on October 16, 1917.
</sample>
<sample number="203">During that time period <loc reading="met">Mexico</loc>, although initially a supporter of the Somoza's, soon changed position and offered support to the Sandinistas.
</sample>
<sample number="204">He then competed at the 2005 FIFA World Youth Championship in the Netherlands, helping <loc reading="met">Colombia</loc> to the Round of 16 before losing to eventual champion Argentina.
</sample>
<sample number="205">In <loc reading="lit">Bangladesh</loc>, where it is known as Ilisha Chandana, it is commercially less important than T. ilisha.
</sample>
<sample number="206">Later orders from <loc reading="met">France</loc> included the Alouette II, Alouette III and Gazelle helicopters, and Fouga Magister and Dassault-Dornier Alpha Jet jet trainers.
</sample>
<sample number="207">He was the son of <loc reading="met">Israel</loc> and Bridgett.
</sample>
<sample number="208">There are representatives of different regions of <loc reading="lit">Ukraine</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="209">The parish church in the settlement is dedicated to the Assumption of Mary and belongs to the Roman Catholic Archdiocese of <loc reading="lit">Ljubljana</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="210">From the 1800s it was a center of Hermanos' religious activity, based upon practices that originated in <loc reading="lit">Spain</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="211">The Soviets want to expand their influence; the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> intend to appropriate the continent's natural riches; the former empires seek to revive their shaky colonial power; and the young nations defend their newly-won independence, armed with an ideal: internationalism.
</sample>
<sample number="212"><loc reading="lit">Uganda</loc>'s 60 conservation protected areas harbor populations of numerous critically endangered species.
</sample>
<sample number="213">He made a useful 43 in the second innings, coming in when <loc reading="met">New Zealand</loc> was struggling at 103 for 7 and helping the side avoid defeat.
</sample>
<sample number="214">She currently lives in the village of Achui, in Guri, outside of the hustle and bustle of <loc reading="lit">Seoul</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="215">San Diego–Tijuana traces its European roots to 1542 when the land was explored by <loc reading="met">Portugal</loc> on behalf of imperial Spain.
</sample>
<sample number="216">After the Safavid conquest of <loc reading="met">Baku</loc> in 1501, the Sufi order was expelled.
</sample>
<sample number="217"><loc reading="met">Victoria</loc> appointed 19 Knights Grand Cross, plus an additional 28 honorary Knights Grand Cross, between the order's institution and her death on 22 January 1901; of those 19, six were to Princes of the United Kingdom—her own children, grandchildren or other close relatives—and a further seven to those already holding a peerage..
</sample>
<sample number="218">Prince August died at the age of 41 of pneumonia at the <loc reading="lit">Royal Palace of Stockholm</loc>, Stockholm.
</sample>
<sample number="219">The route starts at the Canada/US Border in a densely wooded area near <loc reading="lit">King Brook Lake</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="220">The first Long Night of Museums took place in <loc reading="lit">Berlin</loc> in 1997.
</sample>
<sample number="221">It grows in areas with low levels of rainfall and its range extends southwards from Arizona, <loc reading="lit">Texas</loc> and New Mexico in the United States into Mexico.
</sample>
<sample number="222">Does anyone know of any archives that have noted certain changes in the political standing between Morocco and <loc reading="met">Israel</loc> to answer this question?
</sample>
<sample number="223">The Riverland Football League is an Australian rules football league located in <loc reading="lit">South Australia</loc>'s Riverland region.
</sample>
<sample number="224">In 1821, <loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> gained independence from Spain and Nicaragua became part of the First Mexican Empire.
</sample>
<sample number="225">It is the sixth highest honour awarded by <loc reading="met">Romania</loc> ranking just behind the Medal of Faithful Service and ahead of the Order of the Victory of the Romanian Revolution of December 1989.
</sample>
<sample number="226">While travelling home in 1945 he was summoned to return to <loc reading="lit">France</loc> to attend General Patton, at the request of Patton's wife, after the car accident that caused Patton's death.
</sample>
<sample number="227">The southern border is shared with <loc reading="lit">Brazil</loc> and the northern border is the Atlantic coast.
</sample>
<sample number="228">The impacts of climate change in <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> will be complex and to some degree uncertain, but increased foresight may enable the country to safeguard its future through planned mitigation and adaptation.
</sample>
<sample number="229">It is known as Daungdana in Myanmar, Trey Palung in Cambodia, Bhing in <loc reading="lit">Maharashtra</loc>, Palwa in Gujarat, and Seriya in Sri Lanka.
</sample>
<sample number="230">Syria is located in the Middle East at the eastern end of the <loc reading="lit">Mediterranean Sea</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="231">Before 1772 the area was part of Kingdom of Poland, Prussia and <loc reading="lit">Germany</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="232">She was confirmed by the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> on June 16, 2000, and received her commission on August 3, 2000.
</sample>
<sample number="233">After emigrating to <loc reading="lit">Brazil</loc> via Italy in the 1950s, he settled in Rio de Janeiro.
</sample>
<sample number="234"><loc reading="lit">Burnside</loc> is a suburb of Christchurch, New Zealand, located southeast of Christchurch International Airport.
</sample>
<sample number="235">Honoré took the title of Prince himself, and it was only through the protection of France that <loc reading="met">Monaco</loc> escaped total overrun by Spain.
</sample>
<sample number="236">After <loc reading="met">India</loc> gained independence in 1947, Bangalore evolved into a manufacturing hub for public sector heavy industries—particularly aerospace, telecommunications, machine tools, heavy equipment, space and defence.
</sample>
<sample number="237">She left Chile for <loc reading="lit">ustralia</loc> when she was four-years-old, along with her mother, brother and sister.
</sample>
<sample number="238">He was then transferred to III Amphibious Corps, which was preparing for the planned invasion of <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="239">Gulian was born in Marash in Western Armenia then part of Ottoman Empire, immigrated to the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> at a young age, and grew up in Newton, Massachusetts.
</sample>
<sample number="240">Although the official bidding process has not yet begun, Australia, <loc reading="met">Japan</loc>, New Zealand and Thailand have confirmed their interests in potentially staging the tournament.
</sample>
<sample number="241"><loc reading="met">Italy</loc> classified cathinone and all structurally derived analogues (including pyrovalerone analogues) as Narcotics on January 2012.
</sample>
<sample number="242">Restrictions on the manufacture of certain armaments within the 1919 Treaty of Versailles forbade <loc reading="met">Germany</loc> from manufacturing certain types of weapons, such as light automatic firearms (designated as SMGs with barrels in excess of four inches (102 mm) and magazines holding more than eight rounds).
</sample>
<sample number="243">Perhaps specific locations or services use three phases, but <loc reading="met">Australia</loc> and New Zealand both use an internationally-recognised six-phase USAR model (Emergency Management Australia Manual 35, section 1.14 (page 6 &amp; 7) - http://www.ema.gov.au/www/emaweb/rwpattach.nsf/VAP/(3273BD3F76A7A5DEDAE36942A54D7D90)~Manual35-GeneralandDisasterRescue.pdf/$file/Manual35-GeneralandDisasterRescue.pdf (3.71MB)).
</sample>
<sample number="244">The concept has been very well received, and since then the number of participating institutions and exhibitions has risen dramatically, spreading to over 120 other cities throughout <loc reading="lit">Europe</loc>, as well as elsewhere, in Argentina and the Philippines.
</sample>
<sample number="245"><loc reading="met">Buenos Aires</loc> remained there until 1941 when the club disaffiliated from the Association.
</sample>
<sample number="246">Ruffus was an indie rock band from <loc reading="lit">Estonia</loc> that was originally known as Claire's Birthday.
</sample>
<sample number="247">Bennihalli is a village in <loc reading="lit">Belgaum</loc> district in the southern state of Karnataka, India.
</sample>
<sample number="248">He is the Minister of Fisheries and Marine Resources of <loc reading="lit">Somalia</loc>, having been appointed to the position on 27 January 2015 by Prime Minister Omar Abdirashid Ali Sharmarke.
</sample>
<sample number="249">Athletes from <loc reading="lit">Philippines</loc> won total seven medals, and finished at the 21st spot, tied with Syria in a medal table.
</sample>
<sample number="250">He made a debut 2 days later, on 1 October, during the 0-0 draw with his former club <loc reading="met">Sofia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="251">Tokko's original soundtrack was released in stores across <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc> on June 28, 2006 as part of its release with the TOKKO TV series.
</sample>
<sample number="252">It was located in Rindge, New Hampshire, <loc reading="lit">United States</loc>, on a working organic farm with 142 acres (0.57 km2) of field and forest.
</sample>
<sample number="253">During the occupation of <loc reading="lit">Norway</loc> by Germany he was imprisoned in Grini concentration camp from 13 to 21 January 1942.
</sample>
<sample number="254">Richard T. McCrea and William A. S. Sarjeant published a paper describing new bird and mammal ichnotaxa from the Gates Formation in Alberta, <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="255">This action was taken to ensure the fleet would not fall into German hands, as the Nazis had defeated <loc reading="met">France</loc> and occupied Paris.
</sample>
<sample number="256">The Datsuns toured <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> in 2002 with Melbourne band The Specimens and The Casanovas as well as playing a live to air on PBS radio.
</sample>
<sample number="257">The film was shot on location in Aceh, and reports on the Province’s battle for independence from <loc reading="met">Indonesia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="258">Sarah Culberson (born 1976) is a biracial American woman of Mende ancestry from <loc reading="lit">Sierra Leone</loc> on her father's side.
</sample>
<sample number="259"><loc reading="met">Spain</loc> recaptured the city in 1732.
</sample>
<sample number="260"><loc reading="met">Hong Kong</loc> and Japan advanced but neither got any further, losing play-offs for the next round to South Korea and Israel respectively.
</sample>
<sample number="261">It passes through the towns of Dmitrov and <loc reading="lit">Yakhroma</loc>, crossing the Moscow-Volga Canal on its way.
</sample>
<sample number="262">Some residents left the village for <loc reading="lit">Ukraine</loc> at that time.
</sample>
<sample number="263">The Sahamalaza sportive lemur (Lepilemur sahamalazensis) is a sportive lemur endemic to <loc reading="lit">Madagascar</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="264">Its population reflects <loc reading="lit">Syria</loc>'s general religious diversity, composed of Sunni and Alawite and Christian.
</sample>
<sample number="265">Returning to <loc reading="lit">San Francisco</loc> in 1969, Carter turned to longer-term projects.
</sample>
<sample number="266">James Coleman (born 16 November 1968) is a <loc reading="lit">New Zealand</loc> television presenter, radio host and actor.
</sample>
<sample number="267">It is found from eastern Russia to the eastern part of the <loc reading="lit">Palearctic ecozone</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="268">After the fall of France to <loc reading="met">Germany</loc>, Girardeau created a factory for underground forces of free France.
</sample>
<sample number="269"><loc reading="met">Spain</loc> started off the 2012–13 IRB 7s Series with a bang at the 2012 Gold Coast Sevens, defeating Tonga, Wales and England to finish ninth and win the Bowl.
</sample>
<sample number="270">Metropolitan areas in the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> will continue to grow in size due to a growing population.
</sample>
<sample number="271"><loc reading="met">Algeria</loc> severed diplomatic relations with the United States on June 6, 1967, in the wake of the June 1967 Arab-Israeli War.
</sample>
<sample number="272">The type locality for this species is <loc reading="lit">South Africa</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="273">Xan Fielding was born at Ootacamund, <loc reading="lit">India</loc>, where his father, Alexander James Lumsden Wallace, served in the Indian Army, as a major in the 52nd Sikhs (Frontier Force).
</sample>
<sample number="274">FC Magdeburg season was the club's first season in the DDR-Oberliga, <loc reading="lit">East Germany</loc>'s top football competition, having won promotion thanks to a second-place finish in the 1959 DDR-Liga.
</sample>
<sample number="275">March 28: Neapolitan War commenced by Joachim Murat against <loc reading="met">Austria</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="276"><loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> is scheduled to compete at the 2014 FEI World Equestrian Games in the region of Normandy, France.
</sample>
<sample number="277">Many if not most Brazilians in Suriname work as small-scale gold miners in the town of <loc reading="lit">Albina</loc> which has become primarily a base for nomadic gold prospectors.
</sample>
<sample number="278">The <loc reading="met">USA</loc> also received an automatic berth for winning the 2008 Olympic Men's Basketball Tournament.
</sample>
<sample number="279">The Royal Victorian Order is an order of knighthood awarded by the <loc reading="met">United Kingdom</loc> and several Commonwealth realms.
</sample>
<sample number="280">The Treaty of Kiel was unsuccessful, and after the declaration of Norwegian independence, <loc reading="met">Sweden</loc> attempted to recover its sovereignty by force.
</sample>
<sample number="281">Finally, he was Norwegian ambassador to the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> from 1963 to 1966.
</sample>
<sample number="282">Later the children in the camp represented almost all nations of Europe occupied by <loc reading="met">Germany</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="283">In 1956, <loc reading="met">Sudan</loc> gained independence and hostility towards the Jewish Community.
</sample>
<sample number="284">Until 1962, <loc reading="met">Algeria</loc> had been under the dominion of France.
</sample>
<sample number="285"><loc reading="met">The Gambia</loc> competed in the 2010 Commonwealth Games held in Delhi, India, from 3 to 14 October 2010.
</sample>
<sample number="286">A recent IDA survey (circa 2006) showed that more could be done to help <loc reading="lit">Singapore</loc>’s small &amp; medium enterprises, or SMEs, tap the power of infocomm technology.
</sample>
<sample number="287">Under his rule, Polotsk attempted to distance itself from <loc reading="met">Kiev</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="288">The ten elected members were returned from nine constituencies formed from the nine districts, with all districts returning one member except <loc reading="met">Port Louis</loc>, which returned two.
</sample>
<sample number="289">A proposal for yet another constitution is being discussed, to allow <loc reading="met">Turkey</loc> to comply with EU accession political criteria.
</sample>
<sample number="290">In return, <loc reading="met">Britain</loc> agreed to remain neutral in any conflict between the Ottoman Empire and Russia.
</sample>
<sample number="291"><loc reading="met">Turkey</loc>, despite being qualified already, still played at the European championships.
</sample>
<sample number="292">Despite leading <loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> to the 2015 CONCACAF Gold Cup, he was sacked as coach of the national team after an alleged physical altercation with a reporter.
</sample>
<sample number="293">They decided to found an advocacy group after Maxwell's husband, Tim Maxwell, was wounded in <loc reading="lit">Iraq</loc> and suffered a traumatic brain injury (TBI).
</sample>
<sample number="294"><loc reading="met">Tunisia</loc> and Algeria qualify for the final tournament.
</sample>
<sample number="295">9 June - <loc reading="met">Sweden</loc> adopts a law to ban the spreading violent video movies to children under the age of 15, and even hinder, but not ban by law, adults from watching video movies with "brutal and sadist violence".
</sample>
<sample number="296">Cemil Bayik has accused <loc reading="met">Turkey</loc> of protecting and supporting ISIS.
</sample>
<sample number="297">In 2006, Zijin had 49.28 tons of the gold output and the gold produced from mining reached 20.70 tons, respectively accounting for 20.53% of <loc reading="met">China</loc>'s total gold production and 11.51% of the gold produced from mining in China in the same year.
</sample>
<sample number="298">With <loc reading="met">France</loc>, she won the team bronze medal at the 2004 Summer Olympics as well as three team world titles (2005, 2007, and 2008).
</sample>
<sample number="299">Over 5000 were produced in the United States and the older "classic" models are still being built in <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="300">Ramat Magshimim (Hebrew: רָמַת מַגְשִׁימִים‎, lit "Rain-soaked heights") is an Israeli settlement and moshav in the southern Golan Heights, under the administration of <loc reading="met">Israel</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="301">He was selected against <loc reading="met">Pakistan</loc> on the weight of the 89* that he scored for West Zone against the Pakistanis earlier in the tour.
</sample>
<sample number="302">He also arranged for the transportation to <loc reading="lit">Egypt</loc> of hundreds of Allied soldiers left behind after the evacuation, and now being hidden by the Cretans.
</sample>
<sample number="303">They intended to represent Canada but Matthews' request for a release was denied by <loc reading="met">U.S.</loc>
</sample>
<sample number="304">The <loc reading="met">US</loc> didn't send combat troops into Vietnam until 1965.
</sample>
<sample number="305">He has traveled extensively across <loc reading="lit">India</loc> and also abroad in his quest for wild-life photography.
</sample>
<sample number="306">In 1966-69 he freelanced from <loc reading="lit">London</loc> doing assignments for The New York Times, Women’s Wear Daily, and TWA’s Annual Report.
</sample>
<sample number="307">The university's financial program, which was initiated in the 1990s with the support of <loc reading="lit">France</loc>'s larger banks, was intended to prepare students for middle and back-office positions in the trading departments of financial institutions.
</sample>
<sample number="308"><loc reading="met">Spain</loc> was elevated to core team status for the 2012–13 IRB Sevens World Series, following its performance in qualifying at the 2012 Hong Kong Sevens.
</sample>
<sample number="309">Millner was an electoral division of the Legislative Assembly in <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>'s Northern Territory.
</sample>
<sample number="310">Groups interested in freeing Mozambique from Portuguese colonial rule and making it an independent nation emerged in the early 1900s, shortly after <loc reading="met">Portugal</loc> had defeated the last of the native chieftaincies and established effective control over the territory.
</sample>
<sample number="311">Shodhan scored 45 and 11 in the first Test at <loc reading="lit">Port of Spain</loc> against West Indies that followed.
</sample>
<sample number="312">Lachen is a municipality in the district of <loc reading="lit">Unterallgäu</loc> in Bavaria, Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="313">It sends missionaries to Russia, Ukraine, Armenia, <loc reading="lit">Azerbaijan</loc>, Tajikistan, Afghanistan, Israel and India.
</sample>
<sample number="314">If tobacco was used all over the pre-Colombian Americas, why would <loc reading="met">Spain</loc> have a monopoly.
</sample>
<sample number="315">After <loc reading="met">Germany</loc> invaded Poland on September 1, 1939 Artur along with his wife and child escaped to his wife's hometown in the east, the small town of Buczacz (now Buchach, Ukraine).
</sample>
<sample number="316">Among his students were Lola Mora and Victor de Pol, who both developed significant public work in <loc reading="lit">Buenos Aires</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="317">Falzon has also earned one cap for Malta, appearing in a 3–0 loss to <loc reading="met">Slovakia</loc> on 15 August 2006.
</sample>
<sample number="318">On 18 September 1989 she was leased to the Brazilian Navy, and then sold to <loc reading="met">Brazil</loc> where she served as the destroyer Pará (D 27) until 12 November 2008 when she was decommissioned and put in reserve.
</sample>
<sample number="319">It was part of the traditional region of <loc reading="lit">Upper Carniola</loc> and is now included with the rest of the municipality in the Central Slovenia Statistical Region.
</sample>
<sample number="320">He got his international debut for Bosnia and Herzegovina on 31 May 2012 in a friendly match against Mexico on Soldier Field in Chicago which <loc reading="met">Bosnia and Herzegovina</loc> lost 2–1 in the dying minutes of the match due to a catastrophic mistake by Stojan Vranješ.
</sample>
<sample number="321"><loc reading="met">France</loc> was recorded as having a 2-nil win, but received no points in the standings.
</sample>
<sample number="322">The team has just competed in the Suwon Cup in <loc reading="lit">Korea</loc> losing 1–0 to Uruguay and South Korea respectively and beating Nigeria 4–3.
</sample>
<sample number="323"><loc reading="met">Taiwan</loc> first established a minimum wage in 1956, with the Minimum Wage Act.
</sample>
<sample number="324">Also she was a protecting goddess of <loc reading="lit">Rome</loc> and the keeper of the sacred name of the city, which might not be pronounced lest it should be revealed to her enemies.
</sample>
<sample number="325">After education and vocational training in the U.S. and in Germany Otto K. Eitel volunteered in the Hotel Astor on Times Square in <loc reading="lit">New York</loc>, which was founded in the same year by the German emigrants William C. Muschenheim (1855–1918) and Frederick A. Muschenheim, and where his uncle Max Eitel had also volunteered in 1904–1906.
</sample>
<sample number="326">Established in <loc reading="lit">Sydney</loc> in 1977, the King Living brand currently has 14 showrooms in Australia, as well as international showrooms in New Zealand and Singapore.
</sample>
<sample number="327">From 1863 to 1864 he studied in Edinburgh, and he later studied in Copenhagen (1864), Germany (1869) and <loc reading="lit">Stockholm</loc> (1879).
</sample>
<sample number="328">He defected to <loc reading="lit">Mexico</loc> in 2011.
</sample>
<sample number="329">The members were <loc reading="lit">Los Angeles</loc> drummer Steve Young, and later joined in the UK by bassist Mark Sidgwick.
</sample>
<sample number="330"><loc reading="met">Portugal</loc> responded by sending an expedition of 600 soldiers, mostly from the colony of São Tome, under the command of Francisco de Gouveia Sottomaior.
</sample>
<sample number="331">He spent over 3 years in various Japanese prisoner-of-war camps and had been captured during the Fall of <loc reading="met">Singapore</loc> in February 1942.
</sample>
<sample number="332">Before 1945 the area was part of <loc reading="lit">Germany</loc> (East Prussia).
</sample>
<sample number="333">All kickoff times are listed as local time in <loc reading="lit">Moscow</loc> (UTC+4).
</sample>
<sample number="334">The establishment and success of business software services firms in Bangalore after the liberalisation of <loc reading="met">India</loc>'s economy has led to the growth of India's information technology industry.
</sample>
<sample number="335"><loc reading="met">US</loc> had taken an especially active part in similar operations in South Vietnam.
</sample>
<sample number="336">Born in <loc reading="lit">Rotterdam</loc>, Netherlands, Zetteler moved to Milwaukee, Wisconsin in 1848.
</sample>
<sample number="337">Hypopachus is a genus of microhylid frogs found in the Americas between <loc reading="lit">Costa Rica</loc> and the southern United States.
</sample>
<sample number="338">That turned out to be his last Test as he was never again selected to play for <loc reading="met">India</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="339">Most homicides in <loc reading="lit">Switzerland</loc> are considered killings, with the penalty ranging from 5 to 20 years.
</sample>
<sample number="340">In 1972, the Pirus were created by teenagers from neighborhoods and young black men returning from <loc reading="lit">Vietnam</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="341">A conflict arises with the arrival of factory owner, Francisco Romani (Santiago Gómez Cou), a calculating authoritarian who admires the <loc reading="met">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="342">Turnbull was selected to face <loc reading="met">Australia</loc> on the 1952–53 Kangaroo tour of Great Britain and France but had to withdraw due to injury, and played in two non-Test matches in the 1954 Great Britain Lions tour of Australia and New Zealand, before having to return prematurely due to injury.
</sample>
<sample number="343">In the United Kingdom, Ireland, New Zealand, and <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>, the word "raisin" is reserved for the dark-coloured dried large grape, with "sultana" being a golden-coloured dried grape, and "currant" being a dried small Black Corinth seedless grape.
</sample>
<sample number="344">The work was commissioned by Sveriges Radio Radioteatern, the radio drama department of <loc reading="lit">Sweden</loc>'s national radio broadcaster.
</sample>
<sample number="345">He made his senior international debut with <loc reading="met">Jamaica</loc> in 2012.
</sample>
<sample number="346">The whole scheme also revealed a need for a small batch of locomotives to maintain connecting services between London (Waterloo) and the unelectrified area of <loc reading="lit">Southampton Docks</loc> for the passenger Ocean Liner traffic.
</sample>
<sample number="347">The 1882 Australia v <loc reading="met">England</loc> series was at the time considered to be part of another first-class cricket tour of England, by a combined team from the Australian colonies, but the match arranged between the Australians and an England side was later accepted to be a Test match.
</sample>
<sample number="348">Future Force Warrior was a <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> military advanced technology demonstration project that was part of the Future Combat Systems project.
</sample>
<sample number="349">Malków is a village in the administrative district of Gmina Żarnów, within <loc reading="lit">Opoczno County</loc>, Łódź Voivodeship, in central Poland.
</sample>
<sample number="350">24.2% of <loc reading="met">Berlin</loc> voted in favor but the quorum required 25% or more to do so.
</sample>
<sample number="351">Scores and results list <loc reading="met">Australia</loc>'s goal tally first.
</sample>
<sample number="352">He was posted to <loc reading="lit">London</loc> in March 1944 with responsibility for neurosurgery in the European theatre.
</sample>
<sample number="353">As a result of the September 11 attacks, the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> began implementing a range of measures to increase the security of its borders and its identity documents.
</sample>
<sample number="354">The <loc reading="met">USA</loc> lost the opening round game against Spain 90–86, but then went on to win their next eight games.
</sample>
<sample number="355">Orlando had an early 16–0 advantage but allowed <loc reading="met">San Francisco</loc> to pull ahead.
</sample>
<sample number="356"><loc reading="lit">Suriname</loc>, officially the Republic of Suriname, is a country in northern South America.
</sample>
<sample number="357">Although the Agreement is open to all states, <loc reading="met">Ukraine</loc> is the only state that has ratified the Agreement but not the Rome Statute of the International Criminal Court.
</sample>
<sample number="358">However, not long afterwards, the Cultural Revolution took hold of <loc reading="met">China</loc>, controlling many aspects of life and effectively preventing many films from being made.
</sample>
<sample number="359">The Corinthian War was an ancient Greek military conflict between Sparta and four allied states, Thebes, Athens, Corinth, and Argos, which were initially backed by <loc reading="met">Persia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="360">Dominique Lloyd-Walter, (born 17 June 1981 in London Borough of Harrow) is a professional squash player who represents <loc reading="met">England</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="361">Works of Piko's was exhibited widely his paintings: Georgia, Austria, Germany, France, UK, Italy, Russia, <loc reading="lit">Greece</loc>, Yugoslavia, Sweden Etc.
</sample>
<sample number="362">After Somalia's independence in 1960 from <loc reading="met">Britain</loc> and Italy he became an officer in the newly formed Somali National Army.
</sample>
<sample number="363"><loc reading="met">Nepal</loc> further considered the decision taken by the neighboring nations as a hegemonic step.
</sample>
<sample number="364"><loc reading="lit">Recoleta</loc> is a downtown residential neighborhood in the Autonomous City of Buenos Aires, Argentina; it is an area of great historical and architectural interest, mostly because of the Recoleta Cemetery .
</sample>
<sample number="365">Culberson was adopted one year after her birth by a <loc reading="lit">West Virginia</loc> couple and was raised in the United States with little knowledge of her ancestry.
</sample>
<sample number="366">He made his <loc reading="lit">New Zealand</loc> television debut as an actor and writer in satirical sketch show A Week of It, following which he continued to work with that show's stars David McPhail and Jon Gadsby in McPhail &amp; Gadsby and later with McPhail alone in Letter to Blanchy.
</sample>
<sample number="367">The area is known in <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc> for its orchards, vineyards, wineries and restaurants that feature local produce and wines.
</sample>
<sample number="368">The conference ended with the Netherlands agreeing to transfer sovereignty to the <loc reading="met">United States of Indonesia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="369">It was formally taken in use on 30 June 2005 by the Director of the West Siberian Railway as the 23rd children's railway of <loc reading="lit">Russia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="370"><loc reading="met">Orlando</loc> had an early 16–0 advantage but allowed San Francisco to pull ahead.
</sample>
<sample number="371">Kosovo declared its independence from <loc reading="met">Serbia</loc> on 17 February 2008 and Norway recognised it on 28 March 2008.
</sample>
<sample number="372"><loc reading="met">Croatia</loc> was also a puppet state of Italy from 1941 to 1943.
</sample>
<sample number="373">Her first concert appearances took her to Stuttgart, <loc reading="lit">Frankfurt</loc> and Switzerland, and in 1867 she became acclaimed for her interpretation of Liszt's piano music at the Leipzig Gewandhaus.
</sample>
<sample number="374">Released by <loc reading="met">Iraq</loc> on March 3, 1991, Bellini and Cocciolone were the only Italian POW's captured during the entire war.
</sample>
<sample number="375">The remaining five ships were relocated to <loc reading="lit">Montenegro</loc>, entering service with the new FR Yugoslav Navy, with three of them being decommissioned in the early 2000s.
</sample>
<sample number="376">It was hosted in several cities in Finland from September 25 to October 2, 1977, with the final round held in <loc reading="lit">Tampere</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="377">The <loc reading="met">United States</loc> and France both formally recognized Algeria on that same day.
</sample>
<sample number="378">As SR 338 heads down from the summit, it passes between the <loc reading="lit">Wellington Hills</loc> to the west and the Pine Grove Hills to the east.
</sample>
<sample number="379"><loc reading="lit">Knockholt</loc> is also the only part of this Kent Hundred that is in Kent today, although both would not have been true whilst Knockholt was in the London Borough of Bromley between 1965 and 1969.
</sample>
<sample number="380">During the siege of <loc reading="lit">Jerusalem</loc> in the Great Jewish Revolt, he argued in favour of peace; according to the Talmud, when he found the anger of the besieged populace to be intolerable, he arranged a secret escape from the city inside a coffin, so that he could negotiate with Vespasian (who, at this time, was still just a military commander).
</sample>
<sample number="381">In that tournament he started every game and was only rested by Pozzo in the first quarter-final encounter against <loc reading="met">Spain</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="382">Heisch was born June 10, 1872 in Latendorf, Germany, and after entering the marine corps he was sent as a private to <loc reading="lit">China</loc> to fight in the Boxer Rebellion.
</sample>
<sample number="383">South of this is the Homs Gap, beyond which are Mount Lebanon and the Anti-Lebanon Mountains which separate <loc reading="lit">Syria</loc> from Lebanon.
</sample>
<sample number="384">On 13 August 1967, an RVAH-12 RA-5C, BuNo 151634, was shot down over <loc reading="lit">North Vietnam</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="385">After the Indian prime minister's visit to China in 2015, <loc reading="met">India</loc> and China agreed to open a trading post in Lipulekh, which was not welcomed by Nepal.
</sample>
<sample number="386">The early years of the war were relatively stable for Nat and his contemporaries in the RASC, until they were shipped to Singapore, just days before the capitulation to <loc reading="met">Japan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="387">In 1820 or 1821, the <loc reading="met">England</loc> family moved from their home in London to Cardiff.
</sample>
<sample number="388">The government of France along with the <loc reading="met">Soviet Union</loc> organised, trained and armed a large group of Spaniards earlier liberated from the concentration camps where Spanish republicans had been held by the Front Populaire since they crossed the Spanish-French border at the end of the Spanish civil war in 1939.
</sample>
<sample number="389">His breakthrough came with the 1938 film Luciano Serra, Pilot (1938) where he played a First World War veteran who returns to fight for <loc reading="met">Italy</loc> during the Abyssinian War.
</sample>
<sample number="390">Benjamin Khor Cheng Jie (born 16 February 1993 in United Kingdom) is a double trap shooter who represents <loc reading="met">Malaysia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="391">Anna "Annie" Moore (April 24, 1874 - December 6, 1924) was an Irish emigrant to the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> in 1892.
</sample>
<sample number="392">Since the end of the revolution, Mexico and <loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc> have worked together in numerous projects such as in disaster relief, migration and development.
</sample>
<sample number="393">I suspect that <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc> went there and that this Wiki page links to the wrong school.
</sample>
<sample number="394">Norway has an embassy in Pristina, while <loc reading="met">Kosovo</loc> has hinted that it will include Norway in the second wave of embassy openings.
</sample>
<sample number="395">Len Casey won caps for England while at Hull Kingston Rovers in 1978 against France, and <loc reading="met">Wales</loc>, in 1980 against Wales, in 1981 against France, and Wales, and won caps for Great Britain while at Hull Kingston Rovers in the 1977 Rugby League World Cup against France (sub), New Zealand (sub), and Australia, in 1978 against Australia, while at Bradford Northern in 1979 against Australia (2 matches), and New Zealand (3 matches), while at Hull Kingston Rovers in 1980 against New Zealand (3 matches), in 1983 against France (2 matches).
</sample>
<sample number="396">In 2008, the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> underwent a Sharp Decline in Economic Growth.
</sample>
<sample number="397">It also serves as a regional hospital for Norway's Health Region East, which includes Oslo, Hedmark, Oppland, <loc reading="lit">Akershus</loc> and Østfold counties with a total population of 1.6 million.
</sample>
<sample number="398">Scores and results list <loc reading="met">Bosnia and Herzegovina</loc>'s goal tally first.
</sample>
<sample number="399"><loc reading="lit">Egypt</loc> is regarded as the place of origin.
</sample>
<sample number="400">He plays for Liberty Professionals in the Glo Premier League of <loc reading="lit">Ghana</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="401">It was built in 36 months on 370,000 square metres in Las Tablas, a growing area between Madrid and <loc reading="lit">Alcobendas</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="402">May 3: Treaty between Russia and <loc reading="met">Austria</loc>, 21 April/3 May, signed at Vienna.
</sample>
<sample number="403">In June 2015, O'Dowd made his senior debut for the Netherlands in an Intercontinental Cup match against <loc reading="met">Papua New Guinea</loc>, which held first-class status.
</sample>
<sample number="404">The story initially starts by dealing with terrorism at the end of the 20th century, where <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> is the largest economy in the world.
</sample>
<sample number="405"><loc reading="met">China</loc> and the Philippines have competing claims over the shoal.
</sample>
<sample number="406">However, Álvaro apparently did permit <loc reading="met">Portugal</loc> to settle in Luanda and the colony of Angola was born when Paulo Dias de Novais arrived with his force in 1575.
</sample>
<sample number="407">Originally established in Oslo, <loc reading="lit">Norway</loc>, in 2001 by four individuals; Tor Erland Fyksen, Jan Grenth, Eirik Holtedahl, and Raimond Pettersen, having raised approx.
</sample>
<sample number="408"><loc reading="met">Mongolia</loc> participated in the 1998 Asian Games held in Bangkok, Thailand from December 6, 1998, to December 20, 1998.
</sample>
<sample number="409">This marine species occurs in the Mascarene Basin and off Madagascar; off Sri Lanka, the Philippines, in the South China Sea, off <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> and the Fiji Islands.
</sample>
<sample number="410"><loc reading="met">Jackson</loc> had also requested that Uddin build and run him a recording studio within the mansion he was hiring in the UK for the duration of "This Is It" concerts, with designs for producing his next record with Uddin.
</sample>
<sample number="411">It is found in Botswana, Democratic Republic of the Congo, Malawi, Mozambique, South Africa, Swaziland, Tanzania, Zambia, Zimbabwe, and possibly <loc reading="lit">Lesotho</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="412">The Ambassador of the United Kingdom to Haiti is the <loc reading="met">United Kingdom</loc>'s foremost diplomatic representative to the Republic of Haiti.
</sample>
<sample number="413">Because Lebanon was governed by France as a League of Nations mandate 1919–1943, <loc reading="met">France</loc> has long taken a special interest in Lebanon.
</sample>
<sample number="414">Macdonald served as <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc>'s senior trade commissioner in Sri Lanka, the United States of America, and Lebanon in the 1970s.
</sample>
<sample number="415">Brito was born and raised in Caracas, <loc reading="lit">Venezuela</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="416">The story is written from the point of view and understanding of Schtung, a war dog of <loc reading="met">Soviet Russia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="417">The National Progressive Party was a political party in <loc reading="lit">Namibia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="418"><loc reading="lit">Hölstein</loc> is a municipality in the district of Waldenburg in the canton of Basel-Country in Switzerland.
</sample>
<sample number="419">Nepal now intends to solve the issue via diplomatic means with <loc reading="met">China</loc> and India.
</sample>
<sample number="420">Also annexed to the <loc reading="lit">Alcazaba</loc> was a convent of the Order of Santiago, currently home to the council of the Extremadura community.
</sample>
<sample number="421">The bird's range surrounds the <loc reading="lit">Amazon</loc> countries into the Andes foothills and higher elevations of upstream river systems, but is not along the Amazon River proper in the central Amazon Basin, or the central upper Basin; it is in Brazil at the river's outlet, and upstream for about 500 km.
</sample>
<sample number="422">This party is being held at an artistic <loc reading="lit">London</loc> venue with room for approximately 300 people, and is being funded by Ed Saperia, a non-Wikipedian who has a reputation for holding exclusive events all over London.
</sample>
<sample number="423">Pereira began his playing career with Bolivian side Oriente Petrolero he then played for <loc reading="met">Liverpool</loc> and Peñarol in Uruguay before joining Chacarita Juniors in 2006.
</sample>
<sample number="424">I relished the attacking field set by <loc reading="met">Pakistan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="425">After that, <loc reading="met">Columbia</loc> operated in support of the invasion of Balikpapan and took part in the 1945 antishipping sweep in the South China Sea.
</sample>
<sample number="426">1991 – In Dili, East Timor, Indonesian forces opened fire on student demonstrators protesting the occupation of <loc reading="lit">East Timor</loc>, killing at least 250 people.
</sample>
<sample number="427">There are currently 14 showrooms located in NSW, Victoria, Queensland, South Australia and Western Australia as well as New Zealand and <loc reading="lit">Singapore</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="428">During his reign Polotsk was at war with Kiev and <loc reading="met">Novgorod</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="429">Brazilians in <loc reading="lit">Suriname</loc> form a large community consisting mostly of miners.
</sample>
<sample number="430">After the establishment of the <loc reading="met">People's Republic of China</loc> and before the Cultural Revolution, he was credited as one of the top officials in socialist culture.
</sample>
<sample number="431"><loc reading="met">Germany</loc> faces the United Kingdom in the Battle of Britain (1940).
</sample>
<sample number="432">Declaration of the Powers regarding the abolition of the Slave Trade, signed at <loc reading="lit">Vienna</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="433">The University of New Zealand was broken up into four universities (Otago, <loc reading="met">Canterbury</loc>, Auckland and Victoria University) and two agricultural colleges at Canterbury and Massey.
</sample>
<sample number="434">Among the early tasks of the squadron was the support of RAF units in France, and the evacuation of them once the fall of <loc reading="met">France</loc> became inevitable.
</sample>
<sample number="435">Prior to the establishment of British regime over India and entering a peace treaty with Tibet in 1904 AD, Nepal was interpreted as the main route to <loc reading="lit">Tibet</loc> for external trade with other countries.
</sample>
<sample number="436">He died in <loc reading="lit">Rome</loc> in 1917.
</sample>
<sample number="437">The battle ended in a victory for the UN after large numbers of United States (US) and <loc reading="lit">Republic of Korea</loc> troops were able to prevent a North Korean division from capturing the mountain area.
</sample>
<sample number="438">During World War I, he served in <loc reading="lit">Egypt</loc> from 17 November 1914 to 17 July 1915, Aden from 18 July 1915 to 9 September 1915, Egypt from 10 September 1915 to 1 December 1915 and Mesopotamia from 2 December 1915 to 6 May 1916.
</sample>
<sample number="439">Hole in the Rock is a narrow and steep crevice in the western rim of Glen Canyon, in southern <loc reading="lit">Utah</loc> in the western United States.
</sample>
<sample number="440">One year later, in 1839, <loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> and Nicaragua established diplomatic relations.
</sample>
<sample number="441">All of <loc reading="lit">Beijing</loc>'s expressways, except for the Tongyan Expressway, are interlinked with the 5th Ring Road.
</sample>
<sample number="442">In the quarterfinals, the USA team faced <loc reading="met">France</loc>, which held an eight-point lead late in the second half, but the USA team took back the lead and won by eleven to advance to the semifinals.
</sample>
<sample number="443">Guo played for the Guangzhou Pharmaceutical youth team before he was loaned to <loc reading="met">China</loc> in the 2007.
</sample>
<sample number="444">Moso earned 13 caps for <loc reading="met">Spain</loc> at youth level.
</sample>
<sample number="445">Basically, the <loc reading="met">US</loc> has its "War on Terror", and the Israelis just started their own "War on Terror".
</sample>
<sample number="446">The whole scheme also revealed a need for a small batch of locomotives to maintain connecting services between London (<loc reading="lit">Waterloo</loc>) and the unelectrified area of Southampton Docks for the passenger Ocean Liner traffic.
</sample>
<sample number="447">In April 2013, Fernando was selected in <loc reading="met">Italy</loc>'s fourteen man squad for the World Cricket League Division Three in Bermuda.
</sample>
<sample number="448">In Febuary 1931 the couple were having built a low-wing monoplane at <loc reading="lit">Shoreham</loc> airport and planned to fly to India where Freeman.
</sample>
<sample number="449">The Seekopf is a mountain on the main chain of the <loc reading="lit">Northern Black Forest</loc> in Germany between the Upper Rhine Plain and the Murg valley.
</sample>
<sample number="450">Rally Costa Smeralda is a rally competition held in Costa Smeralda, a coastal area on the island of <loc reading="lit">Sardinia</loc>, Italy.
</sample>
<sample number="451">In the wake of the 2010 Haiti earthquake, UNESCO's World Heritage Program is helping <loc reading="met">Haiti</loc> assess the damage.
</sample>
<sample number="452">He arrived at the port of <loc reading="lit">New Amsterdam</loc> in July, 1639.
</sample>
<sample number="453">Meanwhile, the unified Germans held off the Aussies for the bronze in 7:57.35, 45-hundredths of a second under an old Olympic record set by <loc reading="met">USA</loc> in 2000.
</sample>
<sample number="454">If it has its way, <loc reading="met">Israel</loc> will conquer Syria by 2010.
</sample>
<sample number="455">Today, IMSL is a full member of the Asian Association of Management Organisations (AAMO) and <loc reading="met">Sri Lanka</loc>'s sole representative there.
</sample>
<sample number="456"><loc reading="met">Jamaica</loc>'s capture was the casus belli that resulted in actual war between England and Spain in 1655.
</sample>
<sample number="457">The son of Villien Valdemar Aagaard and Florence Aagard (née Brooke), Aagaard was born at Norwich in 1932, after his father's family had migrated from <loc reading="lit">Denmark</loc> at the time of the rise of Fascism in Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="458">As a result of his prominence in the <loc reading="lit">Wellington</loc> community he decided to enter local politics.
</sample>
<sample number="459">The Rimouski Seignory (French: seigneurie de Rimouski) was a seignory during the French colonisation of <loc reading="lit">New France</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="460"><loc reading="lit">Akkaraipattu</loc> massacre happened on 19 February 1986 when approximately 80 Sri Lankan Tamil farm workers were allegedly killed by the Sri Lankan Army personnel and their bodies burned in the Eastern Province of Sri Lanka.
</sample>
<sample number="461">In early October of that year it was abandoned by the <loc reading="met">US</loc>, considered for sale, but was taken up again in July 1878 as the Principal Recruiting Depot.
</sample>
<sample number="462">With the growth of <loc reading="lit">Berlin</loc>, the stockades and gates were moved as dictated by circumstances during the following decades.
</sample>
<sample number="463">The Haitian occupation of <loc reading="lit">Santo Domingo</loc> began two years before her birth, and she grew up under Haitian rule.
</sample>
<sample number="464">The popularity of the Gardel-Razzano duo was in crescendo, touring on Uruguay, Brazil, <loc reading="lit">Chile</loc> and Spain until 1925 when Razzano left his singing career due to throat problems.
</sample>
<sample number="465">In 1990, <loc reading="met">Mexico</loc>, along with the government of Colombia, Panama and Venezuela created the Contadora Group to try and mediate in the Central American crises that was gripping the region at the time.
</sample>
<sample number="466">Before the tour in England, <loc reading="met">Argentina</loc> hosted South Africa, losing the match 33-37.
</sample>
<sample number="467">Copperlode Dam or Lake Morris is a fresh water reservoir dam servicing the city of Cairns, <loc reading="lit">Queensland</loc>, Australia.
</sample>
<sample number="468">He was a Fellow of the Royal College of Physicians of both London and <loc reading="lit">Edinburgh</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="469">First discovered in 1801 in Mexico, vanadinite deposits have since been unearthed in South America, Europe, <loc reading="lit">Africa</loc>, and other parts of North America.
</sample>
<sample number="470">It has been used since ancient times by traders, mendicants and pilgrims transiting between Nepal and <loc reading="lit">Tibet</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="471">The 2012 population of the region was 4,922,723, making it the largest bi-national conurbation shared between the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> and Mexico, the second-largest shared between the US and another country (after Detroit-Windsor), and the fourth largest in the world.
</sample>
<sample number="472">Meanwhile, <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>'s coastlines will experience erosion and inundation from an estimated 8–88 cm increase in global sea level.
</sample>
<sample number="473">After the fall of <loc reading="met">France</loc> to Germany, Girardeau created a factory for underground forces of free France.
</sample>
<sample number="474"><loc reading="lit">Suriname</loc> allegedly has the largest community of Brazilians in any CARICOM nation.
</sample>
<sample number="475">It will replace Eilat Airport, handle all civilian flights currently using Ovda Airport, and serve as a diversion airport for <loc reading="lit">Israel</loc>'s primary airport, Ben Gurion.
</sample>
<sample number="476">Taking advantage of this fact, <loc reading="met">Athens</loc> launched several naval campaigns in the later years of the war, recapturing a number of islands that had been part of the original Athenian Empire during the 5th century BC.
</sample>
<sample number="477">The Persian army under Shahrbaraz capture the cities of Damascus, <loc reading="lit">Apamea</loc> and Emesa.
</sample>
<sample number="478">Russia is sole successor to the <loc reading="met">Soviet Union</loc>, so ties have naturally continued with Russia since the Belavezha Accords.
</sample>
<sample number="479">The result was to have a high powered 4-car EMU at the London end pushing trailer units to Bournemouth where the trailers would be detached and then pulled to <loc reading="lit">Weymouth</loc> by a push-pull equipped diesel electric locomotive.
</sample>
<sample number="480">Nakatsuno Station (中角駅, Nakatsuno-eki) is an Echizen Railway Mikuni Awara Line railway station located in Fukui, Fukui Prefecture, <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="481">Maafushi is one of the inhabited islands of <loc reading="lit">Kaafu Atoll</loc> and the proposed capital for the Medhu Uthuru Province of the Maldives.
</sample>
<sample number="482">Pearl &amp; Dean is now owned by Image Ltd, and controls numerous <loc reading="lit">UK</loc> cinema sites including leading multiplex operators such as Empire, Showcase, AMC and represents approximately half of the UK's independent cinemas.
</sample>
<sample number="483"><loc reading="lit">Beacon Hill North</loc> had a population of 10,693 while Beacon Hill South had a population of 7,312 (18,005 total) according to the Canada 2011 Census.
</sample>
<sample number="484"><loc reading="met">York</loc> was selected to play for New South Wales and Australia in 1928.
</sample>
<sample number="485">Tired by the commuting between <loc reading="lit">France</loc> and Hungary and frustrated by the lack of selections, she decided to fence for France from January 2003.
</sample>
<sample number="486">It would be almost impossible for <loc reading="met">Ghana</loc> to become a prosperous nation without the help of foreign nations, since they can’t export what others won’t buy.
</sample>
<sample number="487"><loc reading="met">York</loc> primarily played as a prop-forward representing Australia in two test matches against Great Britain.
</sample>
<sample number="488">I live in Finland, Region of Kainuu and Municipality of <loc reading="lit">Paltamo</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="489">Throughout his career he composed numerous pieces of meykhana based on modern <loc reading="met">Azerbaijan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="490">Mercury joins the two on their trip to <loc reading="lit">Athens</loc>, intending to put himself between the blushing newlyweds.
</sample>
<sample number="491">Athletes from <loc reading="lit">Mongolia</loc> succeeded in winning two golds, two silvers and ten bronzes, making total fourteen medals.
</sample>
<sample number="492">The decision proved a poor one though, as <loc reading="met">Australia</loc> were easily skittled out for a meagre 63 in 80 overs, taking just over 2 hours.
</sample>
<sample number="493">Her post had the objective to improve public awareness of the European Union and <loc reading="met">Turkey</loc>'s accession process.
</sample>
<sample number="494">He once said he is member of BJP and always maintained that <loc reading="lit">India</loc> is land of secularism and supported the ethos of India.
</sample>
<sample number="495">This marked the birth of the independent <loc reading="met">Dominican Republic</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="496">In the wake of the 2010 <loc reading="lit">Haiti</loc> earthquake, UNESCO's World Heritage Program is helping Haiti assess the damage.
</sample>
<sample number="497">In that season, <loc reading="met">Spain</loc> played in the 2012 Scotland Sevens, reaching the Bowl finals, and the 2012 London Sevens, reaching the Cup quarterfinal.
</sample>
<sample number="498">The women's snowboard halfpipe competition at the 2007 Asian Winter Games in Changchun, <loc reading="lit">China</loc> was held on 29 January at the Beida Lake Skiing Resort.
</sample>
<sample number="499">Being prohibited from visiting both St. Petersburg and <loc reading="lit">Moscow</loc>, Yashvil spent next several years in a compulsory retirement at his estate.
</sample>
<sample number="500">Its area has been mostly absorbed by the growth of <loc reading="lit">London</loc>; with its name currently referring to the Ruxley district.
</sample>
<sample number="501">In the 1994 Peace Agreement between Israel and <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc> it was decided that operations would be transferred from Eilat Airport to Aqaba Airport.
</sample>
<sample number="502">Concepción Bona Hernández (December 6, 1824 - July 2, 1901) was a nursery school teacher and a campaigner for the independence of the <loc reading="met">Dominican Republic</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="503">It is endemic to <loc reading="lit">Ecuador</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="504">Two were bought by <loc reading="met">Austria-Hungary</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="505">The <loc reading="met">United States</loc> named the war after Red Cloud, a prominent Oglala Lakota chief who led his followers in opposition to the presence of the U.S. military in the area.
</sample>
<sample number="506">Following the program, over 250 members of the organization lobbied the <loc reading="met">U.S.</loc> to "support Gen. Petraeus and the War in Iraq" and to ask them to denounce MoveOn.org's attack on "General Betray.
</sample>
<sample number="507">Live from the Point Depot is the first official release of the band's widely bootlegged New Year's Eve show at <loc reading="lit">Dublin</loc>'s Point Depot.
</sample>
<sample number="508">Armstrong visits <loc reading="lit">New Mexico</loc>, where the eighteenth Moon-rocket, to be piloted by George Quinn, is being built under the supervision of the obstructive Ambrose Fothergill.
</sample>
<sample number="509">The result was to have a high powered 4-car EMU at the <loc reading="lit">London</loc> end pushing trailer units to Bournemouth where the trailers would be detached and then pulled to Weymouth by a push-pull equipped diesel electric locomotive.
</sample>
<sample number="510">Garcia v National Australia Bank Ltd was an important case decided in the High Court of <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> on 6 August 1998.
</sample>
<sample number="511">It was the last season where two rival football associations from <loc reading="lit">Berlin</loc> send their champions to the German championship, with the two merging at the end of the season.
</sample>
<sample number="512">Dr. de Capriles was born in Mexico and came to the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> at the age of 13, with no knowledge of English or fencing.
</sample>
<sample number="513"><loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> has qualified one team of four athletes in jumping.
</sample>
<sample number="514">On the outbreak of the Irish rebellion in 1641, Richardson left for England, and settled in <loc reading="lit">London</loc>, where he died.
</sample>
<sample number="515">In 1995 the tower was listed as one of the official historical monuments of <loc reading="lit">France</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="516">His parents, Kazimir J. Wistert and Josephine (Shukis) Wistert, immigrated to the United States from Lithuania in 1894 and were married at <loc reading="lit">Chicago</loc> in 1907.
</sample>
<sample number="517">In fact, if the History of Monaco article is to be believed, Landi, a close ally of <loc reading="met">Spain</loc>, almost gave away the fledgling nation.
</sample>
<sample number="518">It was originally routed between US 127 in <loc reading="lit">Castine</loc> and its present eastern terminus at SR 49 east of Gordon.
</sample>
<sample number="519"><loc reading="met">Ethiopia</loc> made their Paralympic debut at the 2004 Games in Athens.
</sample>
<sample number="520"><loc reading="met">Soviet</loc> Union invades Poland, Finland, occupies Latvia, Estonia, Lithuania and Romanian region of Bessarabia from 1939 to 1941.
</sample>
<sample number="521">Deseret was never officially recognized by the <loc reading="met">United States</loc>, and so Utah Territory was organized by the U.S. Congress instead.
</sample>
<sample number="522">Sun Hai Bo (born (1983-03-25)25 March 1983) is a Chinese male former weightlifter, who competed in the +105 kg category and represented <loc reading="met">China</loc> at international competitions.
</sample>
<sample number="523">Around 3,100 species of flowering plant have been recorded in <loc reading="lit">Syria</loc> as well as about 100 gymnosperms.
</sample>
<sample number="524">In July 1940, the <loc reading="met">Britain</loc> shelled French warships in the port after they refused a British ultimatum to surrender.
</sample>
<sample number="525">It was an island, cut off from the mainland of <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> and isolated geographically, making it ideal for a Penal Colony, and was rich in timber, a resource useful to the Royal Navy..
</sample>
<sample number="526">Many people around <loc reading="lit">Pakistan</loc> request their fellows to bring it as it is not widely available in any other part of Pakistan.
</sample>
<sample number="527">What was <loc reading="met">Russia</loc>'s take on this "Polish invasion"?
</sample>
<sample number="528">His father, John Bird was a London goldsmith with ancestral roots in Cheshire, <loc reading="lit">England</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="529"><loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> and Nicaragua are two Latin American nations that share a common history in the fact that both nations were colonized by the Spanish empire.
</sample>
<sample number="530">Conservation in <loc reading="lit">Uganda</loc> is the protection and sustainable use of the country's rich natural resources.
</sample>
<sample number="531">Kendall's radio messages alerted Scotland Yard, and Inspector Dew was dispatched to <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc> on the faster ship, the White Star Line's SS Laurentic, and arrived in Canada before Montrose.
</sample>
<sample number="532">Laksono is a supporter of <loc reading="met">Iran</loc>'s nuclear program.
</sample>
<sample number="533">From that time on, the <loc reading="lit">Recoleta</loc> has been one of the most stylish and expensive neighborhoods in Buenos Aires, home to private family mansions, foreign embassies, and luxury hotels, including the Alvear Palace Hotel.
</sample>
<sample number="534">The only World Cup which <loc reading="met">South Vietnam</loc> entered was the 1974 tournament in West Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="535">The company's present focus is on lithium and borax mining operations within <loc reading="lit">Argentina</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="536">It has led opposition in the Kingdom to <loc reading="met">US</loc> military action in Iraq and was at the forefront of demonstrations against military action in Falluja.
</sample>
<sample number="537">Cuba was excluded at the request of the <loc reading="met">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="538">Tibbetibaba was a great yogi and guru of <loc reading="lit">India</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="539">Presumably most ancient and underlying all others, though now confined to certain of the more inaccessible parts of the interior of <loc reading="lit">New Guinea</loc> and possibly to some few islands of the Eastern Archipelago, are a number of Negrito or Negrito-like tribes in regard to which we thus far have only the scantiest details.
</sample>
<sample number="540">Wangenheim sent Parvus to Berlin in March 1915 endorsing Parvus' plan that <loc reading="met">Germany</loc> back the Bolsheviks against the Russian Empire.
</sample>
<sample number="541">His parents, Thomas and Frances Montoya, were Roman Catholic descendants of eighteenth-century Spanish settlers to <loc reading="lit">New Mexico</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="542"><loc reading="met">Singapore</loc> competed at the 2006 Asian Games in Doha under the IOC country code SIN.
</sample>
<sample number="543">She died at <loc reading="lit">Stockdorf</loc>, near Munich.
</sample>
<sample number="544">Under the supervision of workshop administrator-turned-manager Colin Lazzerini, the ensemble chose the name Loose Tubes and played its first <loc reading="lit">London</loc> gig in 1984.
</sample>
<sample number="545">Founded in 1893, <loc reading="met">Basel</loc> play home games at St. Jakob-Park, which is currently the largest club stadium in Switzerland.
</sample>
<sample number="546"><loc reading="met">Ancient Egypt</loc> was a civilization in northeastern Africa concentrated along the middle to lower reaches of the Nile River, reaching its greatest extent in the second millennium BC, during the New Kingdom.
</sample>
<sample number="547">According to <loc reading="met">Syria</loc>, Ketyan had a population of 1876 in the 2004 census.
</sample>
<sample number="548">Luke is viciously confronted by <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc> who was also given a USB with the initials 'LH' etched onto it.
</sample>
<sample number="549">It defended <loc reading="met">London</loc> during The Blitz, landed on Juno Beach on D-Day, and defended the cities of Belgium against V-1 flying bombs.
</sample>
<sample number="550">Johansson competed for <loc reading="met">Finland</loc> in the 1920 Summer Olympics held in Antwerp, Belgium, winning the bronze behind Jonni Myyrä and Urho Peltonen and ahead of Julius Saaristo as Finland claimed the first four spots.
</sample>
<sample number="551">The Damen Group shipbuilders, based in the Netherlands, has managed the manufacture of Damen Stan patrol vessel 4708 for South Africa and the <loc reading="met">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="552">In 1943-44, the <loc reading="met">US</loc> acquired 2,284 acres (9.24 km2) to build a satellite airfield for the use of Kingman AAF &amp; its Gunnery School.
</sample>
<sample number="553">France coach Bernard Laporte acknowledged Ouedraogo's outstanding club form by including him in <loc reading="met">France</loc>'s mid-year Test squad for a two-game series against the All Blacks in New Zealand in 2007.
</sample>
<sample number="554">The Invasion of Jamaica was an amphibious expedition conducted by the English in the Caribbean in 1655 that resulted in the capture of the island from <loc reading="met">Spain</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="555">Despite playing a key part in the <loc reading="met">Basel</loc> first team he surprisingly never played for Switzerland.
</sample>
<sample number="556"><loc reading="lit">Hazembourg</loc> is a commune in the Moselle department in Grand Est in north-eastern France.
</sample>
<sample number="557">Bikaner State, founded in the 15th century and persisted until shortly after <loc reading="met">India</loc>'s Independence in 1947.
</sample>
<sample number="558">The Lombard invasion of Italy was opposed by the <loc reading="met">Byzantine Empire</loc>, which retained control of much of the peninsula until the mid-8th century.
</sample>
<sample number="559">It is found in Europe, including <loc reading="lit">Germany</loc>, the Czech Republic and Finland.
</sample>
<sample number="560">Almost a month later the ship sank in <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc>'s Saint Lawrence River after colliding with the SS Storstad, a Norwegian coal freighter with an ice-breaking bow.
</sample>
<sample number="561">This image was moved from Wikimedia Commons, as it was found to be likely copyrighted within <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="562">The immediate cause of the war was a local conflict in northwest Greece in which both Thebes and <loc reading="met">Sparta</loc> intervened.
</sample>
<sample number="563">From <loc reading="met">Russia</loc> with love.
</sample>
<sample number="564">The investigators representing <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> pointed to the possibility of a false glide path signal causing the crash.
</sample>
<sample number="565">As of 1 May 2016, Bejarano earned 16 caps for <loc reading="met">Bolivia</loc> and he represented his country in 5 FIFA World Cup qualification matches.
</sample>
<sample number="566">Range will continue through <loc reading="lit">Mexico</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="567">Darbhanga Lok Sabha constituency is one of the 40 Lok Sabha (parliamentary) constituencies in <loc reading="lit">Bihar</loc> state in eastern India.
</sample>
<sample number="568">Anna Jóelsdóttir (born 1947) is a contemporary artist of Icelandic heritage, now based in <loc reading="lit">Reykjavik</loc>, she is known for sculptural works of painted canvas often created as site specific installations.
</sample>
<sample number="569">The depot closed in 1985 and was then vacant for several years, until the <loc reading="met">City of Lebanon</loc> purchased it from SP in 1996.
</sample>
<sample number="570">Ion Popescu-Gopo attended (but never graduated from) the Academy of Fine Arts in <loc reading="lit">Bucharest</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="571">He immigrated to Canada, settling in <loc reading="lit">Toronto</loc> in 1968 at the age of 18.
</sample>
<sample number="572"><loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc> voted consistently for Communist causes during the 1980s.
</sample>
<sample number="573">He left <loc reading="lit">Ireland</loc> before the Rebellion of 1641 and died in London on 11 August 1654.
</sample>
<sample number="574">In the reply, <loc reading="met">New Zealand</loc> were all out for 206 runs in 46 overs with Daniel Vettori scoring 79 runs.
</sample>
<sample number="575">Kettunen was selected to represent <loc reading="met">Finland</loc> at the 2002 Winter Olympics in Salt Lake City.
</sample>
<sample number="576">At <loc reading="lit">Harvard</loc>, Vir trained as a method actor for six months and performed eight plays with the Moscow Arts Theatre.
</sample>
<sample number="577">Samuel Adams was a Massachusetts statesman, politician, writer, and political philosopher, and one of the Founding Fathers of the <loc reading="met">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="578">On May 19, 2007, <loc reading="met">Indonesia</loc> launched its own version of Deal or No Deal, called Deal or No Deal Indonesia, hosted by Tantowi Yahya, previously host of that country's version of Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?.
</sample>
<sample number="579">After the Indian prime minister's visit to China in 2015, India and China agreed to open a trading post in Lipulekh, which was not welcomed by <loc reading="met">Nepal</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="580">Prior to Australian Federation the island of Tasmania was a colony of the British Empire, and as such was often at war with Britain’s enemies and European rivals, such as France and later <loc reading="met">Russia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="581">She had been sailing from <loc reading="lit">Lisbon</loc> to Liverpool when Musette captured her.
</sample>
<sample number="582">During that time he was also the military governor of <loc reading="lit">Hawaii</loc> (which was at that time still a US Territory) and Commanding General of U.S. Army Forces in the Pacific Ocean Areas.
</sample>
<sample number="583">This is game 4 in Group B between Finland and <loc reading="met">China</loc> in the women's ice hockey tournament of the 2010 Winter Olympics.
</sample>
<sample number="584">As of 2001 <loc reading="lit">India</loc> census Kuneran had population of 1500.
</sample>
<sample number="585">His only for the under-21 side arrived on 17 November 1998, in a 0–0 friendly draw against Italy in <loc reading="lit">Benevento</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="586">Under his rule, <loc reading="met">Polotsk</loc> attempted to distance itself from Kiev.
</sample>
<sample number="587">Following the arrival of Palestinian refugees into <loc reading="lit">Jordan</loc> after the 1948 Arab-Israeli War, she led national relief efforts to help the tens of thousands of refugees.
</sample>
<sample number="588">In July 1941, after the <loc reading="met">Nazi Germany</loc> attacked the Soviet Union, Buczacz was taken over by the Germans.
</sample>
<sample number="589">Mizo Accord an accord signed between the Mizo National Front and <loc reading="met">India</loc> on June 30, 1986.
</sample>
<sample number="590">Azzate is a town and comune located in the province of <loc reading="lit">Varese</loc>, in the Lombardy region of northern Italy.
</sample>
<sample number="591">Ombaka National Stadium is a multi-use stadium in <loc reading="lit">Benguela</loc>, Angola.
</sample>
<sample number="592">The choir tours regularly and since 2002 has performed in France, Germany, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, the Netherlands, Portugal, Russia, Spain and <loc reading="lit">Ukraine</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="593"><loc reading="met">Mexico</loc> will be represented by eight athletes competing in the jumping, para-dressage and reining events.
</sample>
<sample number="594">This category contains the native flora of <loc reading="lit">Gabon</loc> as defined by the World Geographical Scheme for Recording Plant Distributions.
</sample>
<sample number="595">Commercially, "What It Feels Like for a Girl" was successful in most music charts around the world, peaking inside the top ten in over ten countries, including Australia, Canada, Denmark, <loc reading="lit">Finland</loc>, Japan and the United Kingdom.
</sample>
<sample number="596">Whereas she suggests they went but didn't play due to a political issue with <loc reading="met">Israel</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="597">In December 2008, Russian warships visited <loc reading="lit">Nicaragua</loc> at the invitation of president Daniel Ortega, although Wilfredo Navarro of the opposition Constitutionalist Liberal Party said that without parliamentary approval the naval visit would be a breach of the Constitution.
</sample>
<sample number="598">The law of <loc reading="lit">Luxembourg</loc> is civil law.
</sample>
<sample number="599">During first years of European competitions <loc reading="met">Germany</loc> was divided to West and East Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="600">The VI Corps of the Seventh Army linked up with the US Fifth Army, which fought through Italy, in the Alps as the Third Army advanced into <loc reading="lit">Austria</loc> and Czechoslovakia, where it linked up with Soviet forces advancing from the east.
</sample>
<sample number="601">Falconara Marittima is a seaside resort on the Adriatic coast, in Italy, located 9 kilometres (5.6 mi) north of Ancona, in the Marche region, province of <loc reading="lit">Ancona</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="602">Following <loc reading="met">Bulgaria</loc>'s armistice with the Soviet Union and declaration of war against Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="603">IOCC is one of few agencies still working inside <loc reading="lit">Syria</loc>, and continues to support one of the largest humanitarian networks on the ground in the country.
</sample>
<sample number="604"><loc reading="met">Austria</loc> also finished fourth in the C-2 10000 m event at the 1936 Summer Olympics in Berlin.
</sample>
<sample number="605">With USA taking its third straight title since the event's Olympic debut in 1996, <loc reading="met">China</loc> made a surprise packet with a silver medal, in an Asian record of 7:55.97.
</sample>
<sample number="606">After beating <loc reading="met">Canada</loc> in the semifinals, they had a rematch against Spain, for the championship.
</sample>
<sample number="607">The <loc reading="lit">Monaco</loc> event has grown over the last 10 years - the event now takes over the whole of the Le Méridien Beach Plaza Hotel for the entire race weekend.
</sample>
<sample number="608">It is partially set in the (tribal) area between <loc reading="lit">Pakistan</loc> and Afghanistan.
</sample>
<sample number="609">It was during Ottoman rule that the term "Greater Syria" was coined to designate the approximate area included in present-day Lebanon, Syria, <loc reading="lit">Jordan</loc>, the Palestinian Territories and Israel.
</sample>
<sample number="610">Although the film was originally a television documentary, produced for SBS in <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>, it has since been shown around the world at film festivals and presentations on the subject.
</sample>
<sample number="611">The chamber of deputies votes to break relations with <loc reading="met">Nazi Germany</loc>, the chamber of senators does not discuss the project.
</sample>
<sample number="612">The range extends from westernmost <loc reading="lit">Texas</loc>, United States (where it is restricted to the Chisos and Davis Mountains), south through much of Mexico, occurring widely along the Sierra Madre Oriental and Sierra Madre Occidental ranges, and more rarely in the eastern Eje Volcánico Transversal range.
</sample>
<sample number="613">Nicaragua has an embassy in <loc reading="lit">Moscow</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="614">In this post, he is effectively the de facto representative of <loc reading="met">Finland</loc> in Taiwan.
</sample>
<sample number="615">Six countries abstained: Algeria, Brazil, China, Pakistan, the <loc reading="met">Philippines</loc> and Russia.
</sample>
<sample number="616">We Were Enchanted was released in April 2008 on Plug Research and Shrug Records and supported with shows in the Netherlands and the <loc reading="lit">American Midwest</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="617"><loc reading="met">Uganda</loc> was the first to recognize sign language in its constitution, in 1995.
</sample>
<sample number="618">She joined Doğuş Group, one of <loc reading="lit">Turkey</loc>'s leading conglomerates, as the External Affairs Manager in 2006.
</sample>
<sample number="619">It is situated in the La Paz Department, Sud Yungas Province, Irupana Municipality, near the border with the <loc reading="lit">Murillo Province</loc>, Palca Municipality.
</sample>
<sample number="620">People executed by <loc reading="met">Yemen</loc> or Yemeni authorities.
</sample>
<sample number="621">Lebanon has requested that <loc reading="met">Israel</loc> withdraw from the disputed Shebaa Farms and the hills of Kfar-Shouba and return the Lebanese detainees in Israel as a condition for fully implementing Resolution 1559 which includes disbanding of the military wing of Hezbollah.
</sample>
<sample number="622">He competed at world championships, including the 2006 World Artistic Gymnastics Championships in <loc reading="lit">Aarhus</loc>, Denmark.
</sample>
<sample number="623">So, Russia, <loc reading="met">Switzerland</loc>, Portugal, Italy, Spain, Romania, Poland and France get ready to battle for one of the most prestigious contests in the season, the one precisely lifted by Likhachev’s side in the last edition, held in Rome.
</sample>
<sample number="624">In 2013, <loc reading="met">Andorra</loc> had the highest life expectancy in the world at 81 years, according to The Lancet.
</sample>
<sample number="625">He chaired a commission that produced, in 1851, a draft civil code for <loc reading="met">Spain</loc>, most of it written by García Goyena.
</sample>
<sample number="626">It was a formally described district in French Sudan, but in 1895, the border between <loc reading="lit">Sudan</loc> and Senegal was moved to the Faleme River, placing the western portion of the district within Senegal.
</sample>
<sample number="627">He has also asked international observers to study <loc reading="met">Turkey</loc>'s bombing raids against IS militants.
</sample>
<sample number="628"><loc reading="lit">Ngawha Springs</loc> is a small settlement approximately five kilometres east of the town of Kaikohe, Northland in New Zealand.
</sample>
<sample number="629">The creation of the Kingdom created a partition of Polish lands in which the state was divided among Russia, <loc reading="met">Austria</loc> and Prussia.
</sample>
<sample number="630">A cupboard in France is probably different from a cupboard in Germany, or in <loc reading="lit">China</loc>, or in England etc.
</sample>
<sample number="631">NCC works to achieve the direct protection of <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc>'s most important natural areas through property securement and long-term management and restoration of properties.
</sample>
<sample number="632">Had <loc reading="met">Turkey</loc> finished sixth or higher, the seventh-placed team would also have qualified.
</sample>
<sample number="633"><loc reading="met">Russia</loc>'s attempts to create a large Bulgaria in the Treaty of San Stefano led to the British withdrawal from the Protocol and threatened military intervention, quieted only by the Congress of Berlin..
</sample>
<sample number="634">In 1990, Mexico, along with the government of Colombia, <loc reading="lit">Panama</loc> and Venezuela created the Contadora Group to try and mediate in the Central American crises that was gripping the region at the time.
</sample>
<sample number="635"><loc reading="met">Western Samoa</loc> became independent from New Zealand.
</sample>
<sample number="636">Graham Norton is a Gaelic footballer who plays for <loc reading="met">Dublin</loc> and St Brigids.
</sample>
<sample number="637"><loc reading="met">India</loc> were knocked-out as they lost 10–1.
</sample>
<sample number="638">German brewer George Rublein immigrated to the United States in the mid-19th century, arriving in <loc reading="lit">Marquette</loc> in 1849, not long after the city itself was founded.
</sample>
<sample number="639">La Serena was first founded on the orders of Spanish Pedro de Valdivia in order to provide a sea link to maintain permanent contact between Santiago and <loc reading="lit">Lima</loc> in the Viceroyalty of Peru.
</sample>
<sample number="640">It links Uzen in Kazakhstan with Bereket - Etrek in Turkmenistan and end at Gorgan in <loc reading="lit">Iran</loc>'s Golestan province.
</sample>
<sample number="641">He captained the side in his final year at university and represented the British Universities against Bangladesh and later <loc reading="met">Sri Lanka</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="642">Sections of the expressway in Hong Kong and Macau are observed only by the <loc reading="met">People's Republic of China</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="643">The <loc reading="met">West Indies</loc> made their way into the final after defeating South Africa in the second semi-final played at Sawai Mansingh Stadium, Jaipur on 2 November 2006.
</sample>
<sample number="644">He scored once, against Wales, but missed the final tournament, which <loc reading="met">Germany</loc> won, due to injury.
</sample>
<sample number="645">The territory was organized in 1793 to settle the Mohawks who were expelled from the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> after the United States War of Independence.
</sample>
<sample number="646">Three were also sold to <loc reading="met">China</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="647">His arrangements of many popular Polish folk tunes, and many originals as well, are those used today by polka bands all over the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="648">After emigrating to Brazil via Italy in the 1950s, he settled in <loc reading="lit">Rio de Janeiro</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="649">The Iraq women's national football team is the female representative football team for <loc reading="met">Iraq</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="650">Abdul Hakim Asher (born October 12, 1977) is one of the most influential spokespersons of the <loc reading="met">Islamic Republic of Afghanistan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="651">Its tasks were to protect the Presidency, and the national government in <loc reading="lit">Cairo</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="652"><loc reading="lit">Arcadia</loc> is a small town in Victoria, Australia.
</sample>
<sample number="653">myScience is present in Austria, Germany, <loc reading="lit">United Kingdom</loc>, and the United States and also maintains an international site.
</sample>
<sample number="654"><loc reading="met">Cuba</loc> was excluded at the request of the United States.
</sample>
<sample number="655">Selmar Aschheim (4 October 1878 – 15 February 1965) was a German gynecologist who was a native resident of <loc reading="lit">Berlin</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="656">Australopyrum is a genus of plants in the grass family, native to <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>, New Zealand, and New Guinea.
</sample>
<sample number="657">Keeni is a village in Sangaste Parish, <loc reading="lit">Valga County</loc>, in southern Estonia.
</sample>
<sample number="658"><loc reading="lit">Beacon Hill</loc> was a part of the City of Gloucester until it was amalgamated with the new city of Ottawa in 2001.
</sample>
<sample number="659">The route, which largely followed present-day Sweetwater Road, connected directly to State Route 3 (now SR 208) on the north end at <loc reading="lit">Wellington</loc>, via the Wellington Cutoff, instead of the present northern terminus near.
</sample>
<sample number="660"><loc reading="met">Turkey</loc> is automatic qualifier as the host country.
</sample>
<sample number="661">After his return to Lebanon he was assigned for two years as military trainer for cadet officers, then he was sent to the Egyptian Army in <loc reading="lit">Cairo</loc> for a military course as antitank missile trainer before serving in the armored corps as commander of Anti-tank Autonomous Unit of the Lebanese Army in Beirut until June 1976.
</sample>
<sample number="662">The London Protocol was signed on 21 March 1877 between Russia and the <loc reading="met">United Kingdom</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="663"><loc reading="lit">Liberty Township</loc>, one of thirteen townships in Butler County, Ohio, United States, is in the east-central part of the county, just south of the city of Monroe.
</sample>
<sample number="664">Beginning in 1952, <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> classified these as Class 1 or Class 2.
</sample>
<sample number="665">Over the centuries, <loc reading="met">Turkey</loc> has had many constitutions and can be characterized by the steady establishment of a nation-state, democratization and recognition of international law.
</sample>
<sample number="666">Tired by the commuting between France and Hungary and frustrated by the lack of selections, she decided to fence for <loc reading="met">France</loc> from January 2003.
</sample>
<sample number="667"><loc reading="lit">Squam Lake</loc> is a lake located in the Lakes Region of central New Hampshire, United States, south of the White Mountains, straddling the borders of Grafton, Carroll, and Belknap counties.
</sample>
<sample number="668">He made his international debut for <loc reading="met">Bahamas</loc> in a March 2000 FIFA World Cup qualification match against Anguilla and had earned a total of 14 caps, scoring no goals.
</sample>
<sample number="669">In the episode, the Trotters agree to smuggle diamonds from <loc reading="lit">Amsterdam</loc> for Boycie.
</sample>
<sample number="670">Operation Tinderbox was a series of 14 nuclear tests conducted by the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> in 1979-1980 at the Nevada Test Site.
</sample>
<sample number="671">Phytogeographically, the Caribbean region is often considered to include the coastal plains of the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> (including south Florida), Mexico (especially the Yucatan), Belize, Colombia and Venezuela.
</sample>
<sample number="672">Okamule is a village in Oshakati-West constituency, in the Oshana region of <loc reading="lit">Namibia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="673">At the outbreak of World War I, Lang returned to Vienna and volunteered for military service in the Austrian army and fought in Russia and <loc reading="lit">Romania</loc>, where he was wounded three times.
</sample>
<sample number="674">After the war, it was still operated by Poland, Norway, <loc reading="met">Ukraine</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="675">Horncastle was a county constituency in <loc reading="lit">Lincolnshire</loc> which returned one Member of Parliament (MP) to the House of Commons of the Parliament of the United Kingdom.
</sample>
<sample number="676"><loc reading="lit">Suriname</loc> is the smallest sovereign state in terms of area and population in South America.
</sample>
<sample number="677">Parts of the special were shot on location in <loc reading="lit">Amsterdam</loc> and unlike most other episodes was shot entirely on film and therefore not before a studio audience (making it laugh-track free).
</sample>
<sample number="678">In 1940 Northern Transylvania reverted to Hungary as a result of the Second Vienna Award, but it was reclaimed by <loc reading="met">Romania</loc> after the end of World War II.
</sample>
<sample number="679">From then on, and no longer protected by the god Horus, <loc reading="met">Egypt</loc> was at the mercy of Set and his servant Aker.
</sample>
<sample number="680">Independence from <loc reading="met">France</loc> was formally declared on July 3, 1962.
</sample>
<sample number="681">It was described by Bonaparte in 1853 based on a specimen collected in <loc reading="lit">Bolivia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="682">Evidence has been found within the formation at Braggs, Moscow, and <loc reading="lit">Millers Ferry</loc> in Alabama indicating an instantaneous to brief erosional event, most likely a tsunami, at the Cretaceous–Paleogene boundary (K–T boundary).
</sample>
<sample number="683">South Korea participated as <loc reading="met">Korea</loc> in the ninth Winter Paralympics in Turin, Italy.
</sample>
<sample number="684">I base this solely on <loc reading="met">Israel</loc>'s resolve and objective, not on how difficult it is to achieve such objective).
</sample>
<sample number="685">Yakhroma River (Яхрома) is a right tributary of the Sestra River that flows for 78 kilometers through a network of peat marshes in the north of <loc reading="lit">Moscow Oblast</loc>, Russia.
</sample>
<sample number="686">After six months Fielding returned to <loc reading="lit">Cairo</loc>, and was awarded the Distinguished Service Order on 15 October 1942.
</sample>
<sample number="687">Rudolf Thalhammer (born February 1, 1935) was a former Grand Prix motorcycle road racer from <loc reading="lit">Austria</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="688">Australian victory for the first time in <loc reading="lit">England</loc> was widely condemned in the English press, including the publication of a satirical obituary which stated that English cricket had died, and the body will be cremated and the ashes taken to Australia.
</sample>
<sample number="689">It was built on the <loc reading="lit">Warsaw</loc> orbital line, which goes through Warszawa Gdańska station.
</sample>
<sample number="690">The toli shad or Chinese herring (Tenualosa toli) is a fish of the Clupeidae family, a species of shad distributed in the western <loc reading="lit">Indian Ocean</loc> and the Bay of Bengal to the Java Sea and the South China Sea.
</sample>
<sample number="691">By 1992 wild tigers were no longer being seen in China then by 1993 <loc reading="met">China</loc> passed a ban on the trading of tigers and their parts.
</sample>
<sample number="692">However, when the Pacific War ended in August 1945, III Amphibious Corps instead went to North China to accept the surrender of <loc reading="met">Japan</loc>, and from October 1945 to February 1946, Draeger was stationed with a signal unit in Tianjin, China.
</sample>
<sample number="693">The Dutch–Indonesian Round Table Conference was held in The Hague from 23 August to 2 November 1949, between representatives of the Netherlands, the <loc reading="met">Republic of Indonesia</loc> and the BFO (Federal Consultative Assembly) representing various states the Dutch had created in the Indonesian archipelago.
</sample>
<sample number="694">In January 2008, Despotović signed with FC Rapid București in Romania, and continued abroad for the ensuing summer as he joined <loc reading="lit">Spain</loc>'s Real Murcia for three years and €1.5 million.
</sample>
<sample number="695">The Stolen Generations’ Testimonie s project, created by Melanie Hogan, and is an initiative to record on film the personal testimonies of <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>’s Stolen Generations Survivors and share them online.
</sample>
<sample number="696">In 2015, Amber Lounge will be held in Monaco, Singapore, <loc reading="lit">Mexico City</loc> and Abu Dhabi.
</sample>
<sample number="697">The embassy is charged with diplomacy and Albania – <loc reading="met">United States</loc> relations.
</sample>
<sample number="698">The Fiji–France Maritime Delimitation Agreement is a 1983 treaty between France and <loc reading="met">Fiji</loc> which establishes the maritime boundary between Fiji and the French special collectivity of New Caledonia and the boundary between Fiji and the French overseas collectivity of Wallis and Futuna.
</sample>
<sample number="699">A graduate of the Royal Academy in <loc reading="lit">Copenhagen</loc>, under J. L. Lund, he traveled Europe where he sought inspiration, especially from the Munich landscape scene.
</sample>
<sample number="700">Lipulekh (also known as Tri-Corner) is a Himalayan pass between Nepal, <loc reading="lit">India</loc> and China connecting the North Western Cornered Byash Valley of Nepal and Indian State of Uttarakhand with the old trading town of Taklakot (Purang) in Tibet and belongs to Nepal.
</sample>
<sample number="701">Some believe that <loc reading="met">Belarus</loc> planted the device, rigged a show trial and tortured confessions out of the two suspects.
</sample>
<sample number="702"><loc reading="met">Israel</loc> has its own Afganistan which is Syria, and its own Iraq, which is Iran.
</sample>
<sample number="703">The war in Mexico brings fresh and desperate workers into <loc reading="lit">America</loc>, even from Honduras.
</sample>
<sample number="704">He has performed as a ship comedian aboard Carnival Cruise Line between Houston and <loc reading="lit">Mexico</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="705"><loc reading="met">Germany</loc> opens the section from Bad Nauheim to Rockenberg.
</sample>
<sample number="706">But there is an Oakland City University within a few miles of <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc>'s hometown of Lynnville, IN, in Oakland City, IN.
</sample>
<sample number="707">As World War I broke out and <loc reading="met">Italy</loc> declared its neutrality, Balbo supported joining the war on the side of the Allies.
</sample>
<sample number="708">The <loc reading="met">Nagorno-Karabakh Autonomous Oblast</loc> voted to secede from Azerbaijan and join Armenia, triggering the Nagorno-Karabakh War.
</sample>
<sample number="709"><loc reading="met">China</loc> and Romania have a history of several decades of economic and cultural exchanges as part of the Communist bloc.
</sample>
<sample number="710">Jean-René Jérôme (1942–1991) was a Haitian painter and considered one of <loc reading="lit">Haiti</loc>’s greatest artists.
</sample>
<sample number="711">Her breakthrough role came in the epic Christus, which was shot in Palestine and <loc reading="lit">Egypt</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="712">In 1823, the empire dissolved and Nicaragua, along with Guatemala, <loc reading="met">El Salvador</loc>, Honduras and Costa Rica joined the United Provinces of Central America.
</sample>
<sample number="713">The Tegenpartij was the party for all Dutchmen who can no longer stand the <loc reading="met">Netherlands</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="714">The Barbados–France Maritime Delimitation Agreement is a 2009 treaty between Barbados and <loc reading="met">France</loc> which delimits the maritime boundary between Barbados and the French Overseas departments of Guadeloupe and Martinique.
</sample>
<sample number="715">He earned another Cadet Word silver medal in Baku in 2010 after losing in the final to <loc reading="lit">USA</loc>'s Alexander Massialas.
</sample>
<sample number="716">On 20 May South Vietnam lost their opening game 4-0 to <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> and four days later they lost 1-0 to Hong Kong and were eliminated.
</sample>
<sample number="717">The life in France was exciting and while there he travelled around France and into <loc reading="lit">Spain</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="718">Savitt was born in Shumsk, then part of the Russian Empire (now part of Ukraine) and reared in <loc reading="lit">Philadelphia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="719">On a brief non-Test tour of Australia in 1969-70 he hit his highest first-class score (and first century) of 137 not out against Victoria in Melbourne, out of a <loc reading="met">New Zealand</loc> total of 220, having come to the crease at 22 for 4.
</sample>
<sample number="720">The main aim of Operation Mo was to isolate <loc reading="met">Australia</loc> so it was unable to act as a threat to Japanese territory.
</sample>
<sample number="721">The seven Korea- <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> joint productions both received a limited theater release and were broadcast on television.
</sample>
<sample number="722">With <loc reading="met">USA</loc> taking its third straight title since the event's Olympic debut in 1996, China made a surprise packet with a silver medal, in an Asian record of 7:55.97.
</sample>
<sample number="723">Alveopora fenestrata is a species of stony coral that is found in the Red Sea, the <loc reading="lit">Gulf of Aden</loc>, the southwest and northern Indian Ocean, the central Indo-Pacific, Australia, Southeast Asia and the oceanic west Pacific Ocean.
</sample>
<sample number="724">Until 1962, Algeria had been under the dominion of <loc reading="met">France</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="725"><loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> has been designated as one of the countries most vulnerable to climate change, according to the Stern Review and others, due partially to the importance of its agricultural sector and the prominence of its coast.
</sample>
<sample number="726">The Battle of Battle Mountain was an engagement between United Nations and <loc reading="met">North Korea</loc> early in the Korean War from August 15 to September 19, 1950, on and around the Sobuk-san mountain area in South Korea.
</sample>
<sample number="727">He came back to <loc reading="lit">London</loc> and formed Eat signed to fiction records.
</sample>
<sample number="728">The match was part of a tournament in Austria, comprising Japan and <loc reading="met">Austria</loc> as well as Chile and Switzerland.
</sample>
<sample number="729">He made his Twenty20 debut for Free State against <loc reading="met">Zimbabwe</loc> in the 2016 Africa T20 Cup on 9 September 2016.
</sample>
<sample number="730">The National Institute of Aerospace Technology is <loc reading="lit">Spain</loc>'s space agency.
</sample>
<sample number="731">For instance in 1953 the LCC's Draft Development Plan for <loc reading="lit">London</loc> was subject to an Inquiry and the Bermondsey and Rotherhithe Chamber of Commerce objected to the park extension.
</sample>
<sample number="732">Bush's response to the 9/11 terrorist attacks, his actions as commander and chief in initiating and directing the <loc reading="met">Afghanistan</loc> and Iraq conflicts, and his economic policies have been debated heatedly by partisans, analysts, and academics.
</sample>
<sample number="733">Arroyo de Piedra is a pre-Columbian Maya archaeological site in Guatemala located approximately 2-3 km east/northeast of Dos Pilas and 3 km west of <loc reading="lit">Tamarindito</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="734">The <loc reading="lit">Mozambique</loc> rain frog, also known as the flat-faced frog, is a species of frog in the family Brevicipitidae.
</sample>
<sample number="735">He was the eldest son of Konrad III the Red and his third wife Anna, a daughter of Mikolaj Radziwiłł the Old, Voivod of Vilnius and the first Grand Chancellor of <loc reading="lit">Lithuania</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="736">The Ottoman Empire (modern-day Turkey) ruled over <loc reading="met">Lebanon</loc> and Syria from its conquest in the sixteenth century, year 1516, until the end of World War I in 1918.
</sample>
<sample number="737">As a result, the area (in and around the three tributaries that fed into the head of the Connecticut River) was not definitively under the jurisdiction of either the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> or Lower Canada (which the.
</sample>
<sample number="738">The loading for the new cartridge was standardized and mass production began in 1900–1901 in DWM's factory in <loc reading="lit">Karlsruhe</loc>, Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="739">He studied at <loc reading="met">Munich</loc>, from 1855 to 1859 was a member of the staff of the Allgemeine Zeitung of Augsburg, and from 1859 to 1864 editor of the liberal Isar-Zeitung.
</sample>
<sample number="740">The MCA has now established an Automatic Identification System (AIS) network around the <loc reading="lit">UK</loc> coast, for real-time tracking and monitoring of shipping movements from the shore.
</sample>
<sample number="741">Pawo fled Tibet during the uprising against <loc reading="met">China</loc> rule in 1959, travelling to Bhutan and then on the Kalimpong in India.
</sample>
<sample number="742"><loc reading="met">India</loc> has generated local employment though the building of a drainage system for the hamlet.
</sample>
<sample number="743">For purposes of drawing the border, the treaty assumes that <loc reading="met">France</loc> has sovereignty over Matthew and Hunter Islands, but since Vanuatu also claims sovereignty over the islands, the treaty states that the treaty is "without prejudice to the sovereign rights of any neighbouring State".
</sample>
<sample number="744">Later, in the early 2000s, as <loc reading="met">Romania</loc> began to suffer labour shortages due to out-migration of its people to western Europe, they imported migrant workers from China as a result.
</sample>
<sample number="745"><loc reading="met">Iran</loc> participated in the 1990 Asian Games held in the capital city of Beijing.
</sample>
<sample number="746">He was owner/principal of a <loc reading="lit">Houston</loc>-based architectural practice, Ochsner Associates, from 1984 to 1987.
</sample>
<sample number="747">In 1982, he attended the Ivor Spencer School of Butlers and Personal Assistants in Dulwich, a suburb of <loc reading="lit">London</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="748">Ebbinghaus played for <loc reading="met">West Germany</loc> in the Federation Cup in 1970 and from 1972 to 1975 and from 1977 to 1979, playing in the semi-finals of the World Group in 1973 and 1974.
</sample>
<sample number="749"><loc reading="met">Belarus</loc> asserted that the explosion was aimed at undermining "peace and stability" and hinted at possible foreign involvement but also ordered an emergency investigation of domestic weapon storage facilities.
</sample>
<sample number="750">After serving in the House of Representatives from 1976 to 1979, representing his native <loc reading="met">Cabo Rojo</loc>, Puerto Rico, Fas Alzamora was elected to the Senate of Puerto Rico in 1980, representing the District of Mayagüez.
</sample>
<sample number="751">The boom on urban centres such as Rosario or <loc reading="lit">Buenos Aires</loc>, doesn't change the fact they were already very popular on the north of Argentina or Cordoba.
</sample>
<sample number="752">The uprising reflected a change in attitude towards <loc reading="met">France</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="753">They range mostly in the United States, but have been seen in <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="754">Deposits of vanadinite are now found worldwide including Austria, Spain, <loc reading="lit">Scotland</loc>, the Ural Mountains, South Africa, Namibia, Morocco, Argentina, Mexico, and the US states of Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, and South Dakota.
</sample>
<sample number="755">Licensed for generalized tonic-clonic and complex partial seizures in the <loc reading="lit">United Kingdom</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="756"><loc reading="met">China</loc> experiences periodic outbreaks of northern armyworm infestation.
</sample>
<sample number="757">It also supports some of the last stands of <loc reading="lit">Haiti</loc>'s dense cloud forest on its peaks.
</sample>
<sample number="758">Mount Kenya is located in central Kenya, just south of the equator, around 150 km (95 miles) north-northeast of <loc reading="lit">Nairobi</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="759">They are also collected for human consumption, being the most widely used pine nut in <loc reading="lit">Mexico</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="760">In 2004, it attracted over 75,000 foreign visitors to <loc reading="lit">Belgrade</loc> and in 2005 it was the second most visited festival in Serbia with 300,000 visitors.
</sample>
<sample number="761">In 1910 he left Vienna to see the world, traveling throughout Europe and Africa and later <loc reading="lit">Asia</loc> and the Pacific area.
</sample>
<sample number="762">In the 1970s he participated in the Uppsala Theory Circle at the Uppsala University in <loc reading="lit">Sweden</loc> founded by Tom R. Burns.
</sample>
<sample number="763">The <loc reading="met">Netherlands</loc> entry for the Eurovision Song Contest 2010 will be organised by TROS.
</sample>
<sample number="764">The United States and <loc reading="met">Algeria</loc> reestablished diplomatic relations, and their respective embassies in Algiers and Washington reopened on November 12, 1974.
</sample>
<sample number="765">News of the battle provoked euphoria in Britain, and led William Pitt to take a much tougher line in the ongoing peace negotiations with <loc reading="met">France</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="766"><loc reading="met">Germany</loc> were placed in Zone A of the AFC and OFC qualification in Seoul, South Korea.
</sample>
<sample number="767">He quarreled with his captain off the western coast of Africa and was discharged, cheated of his wages, and abandoned on <loc reading="lit">Princes Island</loc>, in the Gulf of Guinea.
</sample>
<sample number="768">In 1838, the union dissolved and <loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc> became an independent nation.
</sample>
<sample number="769">Before Hong Kong's handover to <loc reading="met">Beijing</loc> in 1997, he had produced and presented many programmes.
</sample>
<sample number="770">Following the June 25, 1950, outbreak of the Korean War as a result of the invasion of the Republic of Korea (South Korea) by its northern neighbor, the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, the United Nations committed troops to the conflict in support of <loc reading="met">South Korea</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="771">Its range extends from the <loc reading="lit">Democratic Republic of the Congo</loc> and Tanzania in the north to the Republic of South Africa in the south.
</sample>
<sample number="772">Partial general elections were held in <loc reading="lit">Belgium</loc> on 10 June 1890.
</sample>
<sample number="773">Alexander Bertschler (born 11 July 1994) is a male recurve archer from <loc reading="lit">Austria</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="774"><loc reading="lit">Charleroi</loc> is located about 60 kilometres (37 mi) south of Brussels.
</sample>
<sample number="775">She is the author of several books on <loc reading="met">Russia</loc>'s foreign policy.
</sample>
<sample number="776">PL-4 is based on the American AIM-7D Sparrow IIIa AAM North Vietnam provided to <loc reading="met">China</loc>, after obtaining samples from downed American fighters during Vietnam War.
</sample>
<sample number="777">The finale received positive reviews in the <loc reading="lit">UK</loc> and mixed reviews in the U.S.
</sample>
<sample number="778">He was CEO of the MMO Games publisher Frogster Interactive Pictures AG (now Gameforge Berlin AG), listed at <loc reading="met">Frankfurt</loc> from 2006 until its takeover in 2010.
</sample>
<sample number="779"><loc reading="met">Bangladesh</loc> has plan to acquire eight vessels of this class.
</sample>
<sample number="780">As a result, the 2010 <loc reading="lit">Pakistan</loc> floods were considered "good news" for the ecosystem and population of the river delta as they brought much needed fresh water.
</sample>
<sample number="781">Canarium australianum is a species of trees, native to Australia and <loc reading="lit">Papua New Guinea</loc>, of the plant family Burseraceae.
</sample>
<sample number="782">A few are well known – the roof gardens at <loc reading="lit">Derry</loc> and Toms in London and the Rockefeller Center in New York, the garden at Twyn-yr-Hydd House in Margam and the rock and water garden he built for Princess Victoria at Coppins, Iver, England.
</sample>
<sample number="783">The third aircraft was registered in <loc reading="lit">Austria</loc> rather than the United Kingdom and the British authorities refused to let the airline operate an unmodified aircraft.
</sample>
<sample number="784">Originally run out of her <loc reading="lit">New York City</loc> apartment, Gwynnie Bee now operates from 5 offices in the USA and India and employs 350 people.
</sample>
<sample number="785">The <loc reading="met">United States</loc> had the most success in the event, gathering eleven medals over the six editions.
</sample>
<sample number="786">Suriname's low population density and abundant natural resources have attracted numerous migrants from neighboring <loc reading="lit">Brazil</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="787">The line climbed at 1 in 66 to Hagley Rd, with a break of 1 in 224 through Rotton Park Rd station, and then descended to <loc reading="lit">Harborne</loc> at 1 in 66, crossing the Chad Valley on a high bank.
</sample>
<sample number="788">In 1977, together with his teacher Yuchoku Higa, he was invited to visit <loc reading="lit">Argentina</loc> by the Shorin Ryu Kyudokan Federation (presided over by Jintatsu Higa), of that country for the Argentinian championships of Okinawa Kyudokan karate-do.
</sample>
<sample number="789">She plays on the Angola women's national handball team, and participated at the 2011 World Women's Handball Championship in <loc reading="lit">Brazil</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="790">By the early 20th century, two non-European states, <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> and the United States of America, would come to be respected as fellow Great Powers.
</sample>
<sample number="791">It served the small town of Anchovy, Jamaica on the Kingston to <loc reading="lit">Montego Bay</loc> line and was 105.75 miles (170.19 km) from the Kingston terminus.
</sample>
<sample number="792">Jajit Singh Jallah is an international rowing competitor from the state of <loc reading="lit">Punjab</loc>, India.
</sample>
<sample number="793">Charles de Gaulle despised him and <loc reading="met">France</loc> refused to assist him.
</sample>
<sample number="794">Bosnia and Herzegovina declared independence from <loc reading="met">Yugoslavia</loc> in March 1992.
</sample>
<sample number="795"><loc reading="met">Germany</loc>'s occupation of Norway from 1940 to 1945, he was a coordinator of the cooperation with the Norwegian government-in-exile and the Norwegian resistance movement.
</sample>
<sample number="796">In 1757, he was sent to <loc reading="lit">Paris</loc> to negotiate loans for the Danish state and, in 1760–61, he negotiated a substantial loan for the Danish state in Genova.
</sample>
<sample number="797">William Kyle Carpenter (born October 17, 1989), also known as Kyle Carpenter, is a (medically) retired United States Marine who received the United States' highest military honor, the Medal of Honor for his actions in Marjah, Helmand Province, <loc reading="lit">Afghanistan</loc> in 2010.
</sample>
<sample number="798">Like most developing countries in Africa, <loc reading="met">Ghana</loc> has relied mainly on cocoa, minerals, and timber as the main exports of its economy.
</sample>
<sample number="799">The competition was won by <loc reading="met">Israel</loc>, who was represented by its U-20 team.
</sample>
<sample number="800">January 31 – The <loc reading="met">United States</loc> deactivates its Ground Observer Corps.
</sample>
<sample number="801">It was commissioned in about 1562, by Francesco de' Medici for a fountain in Florence, but was later sent as a gift to <loc reading="met">Spain</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="802">Liguri, or Logorik, is an Eastern Sudanic language of the Daju family spoken by the Logorik people in the Liguri Hills of the Nuba Mountains, northeast of <loc reading="lit">Kaduqli</loc> in South Kurdufan province in southern Sudan.
</sample>
<sample number="803">Techvaganza is a Techno-management festival and is one of the largest festivals in <loc reading="lit">India</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="804">The Embassy of Belarus in London is the diplomatic mission of <loc reading="met">Belarus</loc> in the United Kingdom.
</sample>
<sample number="805">These buses were operated mostly in Czech Republic and <loc reading="lit">Slovakia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="806">Ellen Andrews, an airline employee from Wichita working in <loc reading="lit">Paris</loc>, assists Mickey in locating and retrieving the casket.
</sample>
<sample number="807"><loc reading="lit">Monaco</loc> is known for its glamor and the race attracts the rich and famous from around the world, making it a fitting venue for the Amber Lounge.
</sample>
<sample number="808"><loc reading="met">China</loc> felt the ban would be short lived due to the nation's demand for tiger parts.
</sample>
<sample number="809">Did they go but face other teams and do other events, or find that <loc reading="met">Israel</loc> was going to be there and turned away?
</sample>
<sample number="810">Krüger represents <loc reading="met">Sweden</loc> in international play, helping his country capture a bronze medal at the junior level and a silver medal in senior international play.
</sample>
<sample number="811">It also operated services across the English border to <loc reading="lit">Carlisle</loc>, and from 5 March 1988, took over operation of the Caledonian Sleeper services to London Euston.
</sample>
<sample number="812">In his final year, he took leave from medical school to focus on his religious studies, traveling to Syria and then <loc reading="lit">Pakistan</loc>, where he studied a traditional curriculum for a number of years under some of their greatest scholars.
</sample>
<sample number="813">It connects the towns of Smith and <loc reading="lit">Wellington</loc> to the California state line north of Bridgeport, California.
</sample>
<sample number="814">His artwork has been exhibited in countries such as Canada, Brazil, Senegal, USA, Martinique, Latin America, <loc reading="lit">Dominican Republic</loc>, Europe and Haiti.
</sample>
<sample number="815">Apart from being considered one of <loc reading="lit">Sweden</loc>'s finest actors, he is also a devoted father of three children.
</sample>
<sample number="816">It may be found in Mauritius and the Cambodian Mekong near the <loc reading="lit">Vietnam</loc> border.
</sample>
<sample number="817">Alyssa Jean Anderson (born September 30, 1990) is an American competition swimmer and Olympic gold medalist who represented the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> as the 2012 Summer Olympics.
</sample>
<sample number="818">Similar real-live analogy is, had Axis won WW2, we will now live knowing <loc reading="met">US</loc> and their allies as evil being with Jews as an infection of the world that need to be removed (Thank God Alliance won).
</sample>
<sample number="819">The Danes attack <loc reading="met">Estonia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="820">Beretić represented Serbia and <loc reading="met">Montenegro</loc> at the 2004 Summer Olympics.
</sample>
<sample number="821">This source does not verify that "<loc reading="met">Saudi Arabia</loc> donated over US$3.3 million, more than any other country".
</sample>
<sample number="822">He is most famous for playing for the Hungarian national team at the 1986 FIFA World Cup in Mexico, where <loc reading="met">Hungary</loc> failed to progress from the group stage.
</sample>
<sample number="823">Brunel remained in the United States for six years, sailing for <loc reading="lit">England</loc> in February 1799.
</sample>
<sample number="824">It is bordered by Turkey to the north, Lebanon and <loc reading="lit">Israel</loc> to the west, Jordan to the south and Iraq to the east.
</sample>
<sample number="825">They qualified for the 2011 Youth World Cup in Columbia by beating the Solomon Islands 3–0, New Caledonia 10–0, Fiji 6–0 and won the Final 3–1 over the <loc reading="met">Solomon Islands</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="826">Mexico–Nicaragua relations refers to the diplomatic relations between Mexico and <loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="827">At the same time, Stanisław secretly talks with the Teutonic Knights for a ceasefire, which finally took place in December 1520, a few months before a peace treaty ended for good the war between <loc reading="met">Poland</loc> and the Teutonic Order.
</sample>
<sample number="828">Abdul Hakim Asher was born on October 12, 1977 in the Bagram district of Parwan province in central <loc reading="lit">Afghanistan</loc> north of Kabul.
</sample>
<sample number="829">A former high voltage line help to place the power plant there, because since the 1970s <loc reading="met">Ukraine</loc> was a large electricity supplier of Hungary through the Albertirsa-Zahidnoukrainska 750 kV transmission line.
</sample>
<sample number="830">Before Spain he represented his native <loc reading="met">Cuba</loc>, competing at the 1991 World Championships where he reached the semifinals.
</sample>
<sample number="831">Groups interested in freeing <loc reading="met">Mozambique</loc> from Portuguese colonial rule and making it an independent nation emerged in the early 1900s, shortly after Portugal had defeated the last of the native chieftaincies and established effective control over the territory.
</sample>
<sample number="832">The hospital is responsible for providing health care to 170,000 people residing in the northern part of <loc reading="lit">Oslo</loc> as well as the municipalities of Ski, Oppegård, Nesodden, Frogn, Ås and Vestby.
</sample>
<sample number="833">The 1971 Cupa României Final was the 33rd final of <loc reading="lit">Romania</loc>'s most prestigious football cup competition.
</sample>
<sample number="834">In September 2008, perhaps in response to Nicaragua's support over the breakaway Georgian territories, Russia offered to strengthen ties with Nicaragua and to provide aid to <loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc> to help rebuild areas damaged by hurricanes.
</sample>
<sample number="835">He returned to <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc> to complete officer training and attained the rank of Pilot Officer.
</sample>
<sample number="836">The Royal Charter of 27 March 1668 was an agreement between the <loc reading="met">Kingdom of England</loc> and the English East India Company.
</sample>
<sample number="837">In the show, he uses an Autovox to create amateur-like reports in <loc reading="lit">Italy</loc> and abroad.
</sample>
<sample number="838">March 25: Treaty of Vienna, between Great Britain, Austria, Russia, and <loc reading="met">Prussia</loc>, confirming the principles on which they had acted by the Treaty of Chaumont, March 1, 1814.
</sample>
<sample number="839">He pioneered the concept of the nation as a brand and has worked on branding projects for a number of cities and countries, including London, Mauritius, <loc reading="lit">Northern Ireland</loc>, Poland, Portugal, and Lithuania.
</sample>
<sample number="840">Nevertheless, the withdrawal of <loc reading="met">US</loc> made it possible for North Vietnamese forces to quickly regain control of the valley.
</sample>
<sample number="841">He also featured in the Zambian team that hosted Kenya, <loc reading="met">Uganda</loc> and Ghana during Zambia's independence celebrations in October of the same year.
</sample>
<sample number="842">It lies just east of the main motorway from Ljubljana to <loc reading="lit">Maribor</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="843">Participating nations were: titleholders Australia, Great Britain, Netherlands, <loc reading="met">Pakistan</loc>, Soviet Union and Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="844">The next year, Pereira was the captain of <loc reading="met">New Zealand</loc> who won the OFC U-20s, and was given the Golden Ball as the best player of the tournament.
</sample>
<sample number="845"><loc reading="met">Australia</loc> and California are now the two leading producers.
</sample>
<sample number="846">Nine countries voted in favor: Angola, Benin, Chile, France, Germany, Romania, <loc reading="met">Spain</loc>, the United Kingdom, and the United States.
</sample>
<sample number="847">At the time of its completion in 2006, it was the 11th-tallest skyscraper in Turkey and the tallest in Konya and the <loc reading="lit">Central Anatolia Region</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="848">It is located near the north-western shore of the <loc reading="lit">Gulf of Panama</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="849">His only for the under-21 side arrived on 17 November 1998, in a 0–0 friendly draw against <loc reading="met">Italy</loc> in Benevento.
</sample>
<sample number="850">As <loc reading="met">Australia</loc> rose to dominance in the 1990s Matthews proved to be "not good enough in either of the game's main departments to make a lasting impact as a Test all-rounder" and despite a century against England in 1990-91 he played only irregularly and was finally dropped in 1993.
</sample>
<sample number="851">The second USS Charleston (C-2) was a United States Navy protected cruiser — the fourth <loc reading="met">US</loc> protected cruiser to be built.
</sample>
<sample number="852"><loc reading="lit">Hokagon Island</loc> is an island located within Coronation Gulf, south of Victoria Island, in the Kitikmeot Region, Nunavut, Canada.
</sample>
<sample number="853"><loc reading="met">Spain</loc> was one of the 15 core teams participating in all nine tournaments during the 2012–13 IRB Sevens World Series.
</sample>
<sample number="854">He wandered in Europe, then came to South America where he travelled in Venezuela, Colombia, Ecuador, Peru and finally <loc reading="lit">Brazil</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="855">In 1975 <loc reading="met">Suriname</loc> gained full independence from the Netherlands.
</sample>
<sample number="856"><loc reading="met">Chelsea</loc> fans did not list any of the trio from West London, instead selecting Arsenal, Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United.
</sample>
<sample number="857">It was founded in 1942, as the National Institute of Aeronautics, and has its headquarters in Torrejón de Ardoz, near <loc reading="lit">Madrid</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="858">He spent his childhood in <loc reading="lit">Dhaka</loc> where he studied at Dhaka Collegiate School.
</sample>
<sample number="859">In 1985 during the Soviet War in Afghanistan, Hakim Asher's family decided to leave their home for <loc reading="lit">Pakistan</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="860">On 1 July 2011, Despotović signed for <loc reading="lit">Japan</loc>'s Urawa Red Diamonds.
</sample>
<sample number="861">After the fall of France to Germany, Girardeau created a factory for underground forces of free <loc reading="met">France</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="862">During Napoleon's invasion of <loc reading="lit">Russia</loc> in 1812, Yashvil managed to obtain permission from General Dmitry Shepelev to join the Kaluga militia and helped recover Yelnya.
</sample>
<sample number="863">She also participated for <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> at the 1996 Summer Olympics.
</sample>
<sample number="864">Trevor Immelman of <loc reading="lit">South Africa</loc> won the 2008 Masters Tournament at the Augusta National Golf Club.
</sample>
<sample number="865">Consequently, <loc reading="lit">Australia</loc>'s annual average temperatures are projected to increase 0.4–2.0 °C above 1990 levels by the year 2030, and 1–6 °C by 2070.
</sample>
<sample number="866">It therefore found itself at the heart of <loc reading="met">Russia</loc>'s strategy for further development of the entire Ural region.
</sample>
<sample number="867">Armando began his soccer career early, playing for the local team, <loc reading="met">Bombarralense</loc>, in Portugal as a youth.
</sample>
<sample number="868">The last name Uslar is of German origin and can be traced back to Johann von Uslar, who fought for the rebel cause during <loc reading="met">Venezuela</loc>’s independence wars.
</sample>
<sample number="869">She was the ancestor of many political people including Lyndon Baines Johnson, 36th president of the United States; Winston Leonard Spencer-Churchill, 63rd Prime Minister of the <loc reading="lit">United Kingdom</loc>; Prince Albert II of Monaco; Princess Diana and Prince Charles.
</sample>
<sample number="870">Bessenbach is a river of Bavaria, <loc reading="lit">Germany</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="871">The name was taken from the location of the crimes, which were committed around the M25, <loc reading="lit">London</loc>'s orbital motorway, during the early hours of 16 December 1988.
</sample>
<sample number="872">The station opened in 1976 at the same time as lines 13 and 14 were linked across <loc reading="lit">Paris</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="873"><loc reading="met">Benfica</loc> qualified for the SuperCup by winning the 1990–91 Primeira Divisão, whilst Porto qualified for the Supertaça by winning the 1990–91 Taça de Portugal.
</sample>
<sample number="874">The Forbes-Robinson's main family home was located at 22 Bedford Square in the heart of <loc reading="lit">London</loc>'s Bloomsbury district.
</sample>
<sample number="875">Her baptism was conducted with special solemnity, being organizated by her uncles Maximilian III, Archduke of Austria and Prince Ferdinand of <loc reading="lit">Bavaria</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="876">This small University was in <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc>'s day called Oakland City College as well.
</sample>
<sample number="877">With Andrei Dîrzu, he took part in <loc reading="met">Romania</loc>'s doubles rubber against West Germany in their World Group Relegation Play-off.
</sample>
<sample number="878">In 2008 Jason Shoultz explored overseas grain trade with <loc reading="met">China</loc> and Taiwan in a special entitled "Journey of the Corn."
</sample>
<sample number="879">In June 2012 the British Foreign Secretary announced that the <loc reading="met">UK</loc> will open a new embassy in Haiti.
</sample>
<sample number="880">This challenges the claim by <loc reading="met">London</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="881">In August 2005, Gómez received a call-up to the Venezuela squad from coach Richard Paez, making his debut on 17 August in a 3–1 friendly match defeat against <loc reading="met">Ecuador</loc>, and scoring his first goal on 1 March 2006 during another.
</sample>
<sample number="882">Like all of the other expansion teams, they finished in the bottom half of the table, tied with <loc reading="met">Mexico</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="883">Wahleach Lake, commonly known as Jones Lake, is a lake and reservoir located in the <loc reading="lit">Skagit Range</loc> in the Lower Mainland of British Columbia, Canada, east of the city of Chilliwack and southwest of the town of Hope.
</sample>
<sample number="884">It is a competition for domestic-league football players from the eight UEMOA member countries: Mali, Côte d'Ivoire, Burkina Faso, Niger, <loc reading="met">Togo</loc>, Benin, Senegal and Guinea-Bissau.
</sample>
<sample number="885">Attaching himself afterwards to François de Tournon, he accompanied him in 1554 to <loc reading="lit">Italy</loc>, whence he was several times sent on embassies to the king, with reports on the siege of Siena.
</sample>
<sample number="886">In 1937, the first of the Somoza presidents of <loc reading="lit">Nicaragua</loc> took power.
</sample>
<sample number="887"><loc reading="met">South China</loc> won the championship.
</sample>
<sample number="888">In 1918 the <loc reading="met">U.S.</loc> acquired her from her owner, the Thames Towboat Company of New London, Connecticut, for use during World War I, assigned her the naval registry identification number 3507, and placed her in service as USS Captain Dud (ID-3507).
</sample>
<sample number="889"><loc reading="met">India</loc>'s Rail Budget is the Annual Financial Statement of the state-owned Indian Railways, which handles rail transport in India.
</sample>
<sample number="890">The airport was originally built by engineers from the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc> in the late 1950s.
</sample>
<sample number="891">After making his <loc reading="met">Spain</loc> debut on 7 September 1994, in an UEFA Euro 1996 qualifier against Cyprus (90 minutes, 2–1 away win), Amavisca appeared in the tournament's final stages, playing four matches.
</sample>
<sample number="892">Jane Mackenzie (née Sym; March 22, 1825 – March 30, 1893) was the second wife of Alexander Mackenzie, the second Prime Minister of <loc reading="lit">Canada</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="893">Williams Régala is a former member of <loc reading="lit">Haiti</loc>'s National Council of Government.
</sample>
<sample number="894"><loc reading="met">Dallas</loc> spent many years in the service of the Honourable East India Company.
</sample>
<sample number="895">The arrival of the convicts was a surprise to many of the Swan River Colony settlers, as <loc reading="met">Western Australia</loc> had petitioned for convicts but had not yet received a reply when Scindian arrived.
</sample>
<sample number="896">It was this treaty that led to the emirates being called the Trucial States before independence in 1971 saw the foundation of the <loc reading="met">United Arab Emirates</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="897">For <loc reading="met">France</loc>, this validated the claim that it was impossible to operate tight ensnaring operations in Vietnam's jungle, due to the slow movement of their troops, and a foreknowledge by the enemy, which was difficult to prevent.
</sample>
<sample number="898">It was heavily damaged in the 2004 tsunami which impacted on over 100,000 of the <loc reading="lit">Maldives</loc> 300,000 population.
</sample>
<sample number="899">The village was named after <loc reading="lit">Bremen</loc>, in Germany.
</sample>
<sample number="900">From that place he sought help from <loc reading="met">Portugal</loc> to restore him to the throne and expel the Jagas.
</sample>
<sample number="901">Farmlands come into view as the highway approaches its junction with Wellington Road (SR 829), which heads towards <loc reading="lit">Wellington</loc> and points west.
</sample>
<sample number="902">During the period, the Meeting Point remained its warm relationship with <loc reading="met">Beijing</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="903">He was capped 18 times by <loc reading="met">England</loc> and gaining two Football League championship medals with Manchester United before he died in February 1958, aged 21, from injuries sustained in the Munich air disaster.
</sample>
<sample number="904">The <loc reading="met">United States</loc>, a member of the UN, subsequently dispatched ground forces to the Korean peninsula with the goal of pushing back the North Korean invasion and preventing South Korea from collapsing.
</sample>
<sample number="905">After emigrating to Brazil via <loc reading="lit">Italy</loc> in the 1950s, he settled in Rio de Janeiro.
</sample>
<sample number="906">The next day before school, Luke and <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc> watch a recorded message of Ketterley and Calvin discussing the Cooperative's plot to wipe out the world outside of Phoenix in 100 days' time with an unknown called "Tabitha".
</sample>
<sample number="907">In 1984, the Royal Canadian Mounted Police investigated allegations that Macdonald had given confidential Canadian trade documents to <loc reading="met">Iraq</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="908">But after it was purchased by <loc reading="met">New Zealand</loc>, the center was subsequently renamed.
</sample>
<sample number="909">In 1929, he was invited to a trial with the full <loc reading="met">England</loc> side and was included in the Football Association XI for a tour of South Africa and Rhodesia the same year.
</sample>
<sample number="910"><loc reading="met">Iran</loc>'s nuclear program began in 1959 with a small reactor given by the United States to Tehran University as part of the "Atoms for Peace" program announced by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in December 1953.
</sample>
<sample number="911"><loc reading="lit">Haiti</loc> has a World Heritage site located here.
</sample>
<sample number="912">As a 'bright young thing' along with Lady Diana Cooper and Elsa Maxwell, Blossom organised 'treasure hunt' parties across <loc reading="lit">London</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="913">Library technician at the State Library of <loc reading="lit">News South Wales</loc> in Sydney Australia.
</sample>
<sample number="914">Nicaragua–Russia relations are the relationships between the two countries, Russia and <loc reading="met">Nicaragua</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="915">In the United Kingdom, United States, India, and <loc reading="lit">Brazil</loc> diclofenac may be supplied as either the sodium or potassium salt; in China, it is most often supplied as the sodium salt, while in some other countries it is only available as the potassium salt.
</sample>
<sample number="916">This marine species occurs in the Indian Ocean (Tanzania, Mascarene Islands) and eastwards as far as <loc reading="lit">Indonesia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="917">It was announced that loan signing Jamal Fakir would be returning home to <loc reading="lit">France</loc> to join Lezignan after his loan expired in the off season.
</sample>
<sample number="918">Peter Plympton Smith (born October 31, 1945) is a former member of the United States House of Representatives from the U.S. state of <loc reading="lit">Vermont</loc>, the 75th Lieutenant Governor of Vermont, and an education administrator.
</sample>
<sample number="919"><loc reading="met">Australia</loc> continued their successful mid-1990s run by winning the bronze medal at the 1998 World Aquatics Championships in Perth, and remarkably over the rest of 1998 and 1999 were unbeatable, winning the four international tournaments they contested in the Netherlands, Italy, the United States and Hungary.
</sample>
<sample number="920"><loc reading="lit">Meslières</loc> is a commune in the Doubs département in the Bourgogne-Franche-Comté region in eastern France.
</sample>
<sample number="921">The Bv 202 was designed to transport troops and equipment through snow or boglands in the northern parts of <loc reading="lit">Sweden</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="922">Saint Andrew ("St. Andrew") is one of eleven parishes of <loc reading="lit">Barbados</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="923">He distinguished himself in the storming of <loc reading="lit">Belgrade</loc> in 1789.
</sample>
<sample number="924">In September 2008, perhaps in response to Nicaragua's support over the breakaway Georgian territories, <loc reading="met">Russia</loc> offered to strengthen ties with Nicaragua and to provide aid to Nicaragua to help rebuild areas damaged by hurricanes.
</sample>
<sample number="925">It is found in most of central, and eastern South America proper, in Argentina, Bolivia, Brazil, Colombia, Ecuador, French Guiana, Guyana, Suriname-(the Guianas), <loc reading="lit">Paraguay</loc>, Peru, and Venezuela.
</sample>
<sample number="926">Heraclius mobilises a Byzantine expeditionary force to Antioch (Syria), but is completely defeated outside the city by <loc reading="met">Persia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="927"><loc reading="met">Nepal</loc> now intends to solve the issue via diplomatic means with China and India.
</sample>
<sample number="928">A respected journalist, he was a proponent of the separation of religion and state, and an advocate of dialogue and conciliation with <loc reading="met">Greece</loc>, as well as of human rights for various minorities in Turkey.
</sample>
<sample number="929">He was switched from his original position of centre to the right wing by <loc reading="met">Wales</loc> coach Clive Rowlands on their 1969 tour of Australia and New Zealand, and thereafter played in that position.
</sample>
<sample number="930">Israel has its own Afganistan which is Syria, and its own <loc reading="met">Iraq</loc>, which is Iran.
</sample>
<sample number="931">She is also the founder of a medical student curriculum called "The Healer's Art" used in medical schools throughout the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="932">Alon Ben-Meir (born 1937) is an American expert on Middle East politics and affairs, specializing in peace negotiations between Israel and the <loc reading="met">Arab</loc> states.
</sample>
<sample number="933">The park is located adjacent to a Telecommunication Company of Iran Satellite Earth Station, at the foot of the <loc reading="lit">Alborz</loc> mountains.
</sample>
<sample number="934">Prior to his Twenty20 debut, he was part of <loc reading="met">South Africa</loc>'s squad for the 2016 Under-19 Cricket World Cup.
</sample>
<sample number="935">Following the June 25, 1950, outbreak of the Korean War as a result of the invasion of the Republic of Korea (South Korea) by its northern neighbor, the <loc reading="met">Democratic People's Republic of Korea</loc>, the United Nations committed troops to the conflict in support of South Korea.
</sample>
<sample number="936">The resolution was sponsored by France and the <loc reading="met">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="937">In 1981, the area of Golan was unilaterally annexed by <loc reading="met">Israel</loc>, abolishing military occupation system and imposing Israeli civil rule on the area.
</sample>
<sample number="938">January 28 – An act of the <loc reading="met">U.S.</loc> designates the United States Coast Guard, begun in 1790, as a military branch over 19 years.
</sample>
<sample number="939">While working on the album she enlisted the help of producer <loc reading="met">Bangladesh</loc> so that she could give her music a more distinct edge.
</sample>
<sample number="940">The ship's hijacking and subsequent events remain mysterious as no credible explanation exists of its disappearance and <loc reading="met">Russia</loc>'s conduct during and after capturing the ship.
</sample>
<sample number="941">It lives throughout the eastern United States and Canada and occasionally down into <loc reading="lit">Mexico</loc>, and is one of the more commonly encountered day-flying moths in the region, easily recognized by the two bright yellow bands across the abdomen.
</sample>
<sample number="942">When he was released Kelly came clean about her affair with Scott and revealed to Roy that she planned to start a new life in <loc reading="lit">London</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="943">At the same games in Athens, Greece, Târlea helped <loc reading="met">Romania</loc> to sixth place in the 4 × 400 m relay.
</sample>
<sample number="944">She represented the <loc reading="lit">Chinese Taipei</loc> national team in two editions of the Olympic Games (2004 and 2008).
</sample>
<sample number="945"><loc reading="lit">Clinton</loc> is an unincorporated census-designated place (CDP) in Prince George's County, Maryland, United States.
</sample>
<sample number="946">In <loc reading="lit">Finland</loc> this style of cap was adopted first in 1918, by Civic Guard, and in 1936 by the Army.
</sample>
<sample number="947">Syria remained the Umayyads' main power base thereafter, and <loc reading="lit">Damascus</loc> was their capital.
</sample>
<sample number="948">R&amp;B Songs is a chart released weekly by Billboard in the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="949">In July 1941, after the Nazi Germany attacked the Soviet Union, Buczacz was taken over by the <loc reading="met">Germany</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="950">Despite ideological sympathy, Franco did not bring <loc reading="met">Spain</loc> into the war as a belligerent and stationed field armies in the Pyrenees to dissuade a German occupation of the Iberian Peninsula.
</sample>
<sample number="951">In 2005-06, St. Jakob-Park attracted an average attendance of 23,500, making <loc reading="met">Basel</loc> the most highly supported football club in Switzerland.
</sample>
<sample number="952">The song was also produced by <loc reading="met">Bangladesh</loc>, Dr. Luke and Benny Blanco with engineering done by Emily Wright, Sam Holland, Chris "TEK" O'Ryan and Chris Holmes.
</sample>
<sample number="953">Following a series of such attacks extending to the coast of <loc reading="lit">India</loc>, a British expeditionary force was sent to Ras Al Khaimah and sacked the town, setting it to fire and also burning the vessels, 'upwards of fifty', in the port.
</sample>
<sample number="954">This was not only a reaction to the Contra resistance movement but a full-fledged alliance with <loc reading="met">Soviet Union</loc>, which provided free credit, economic subsidies and heavy weapon grants.
</sample>
<sample number="955"><loc reading="lit">Czaszyn</loc> is currently situated in the Subcarpathian Voivodship (since 1999), previously in Krosno Voivodship (1975–1998) and Sanok district, (10 miles east of Sanok), located near the towns of Medzilaborce and Palota (in northeastern Slovakia).
</sample>
<sample number="956">After the creation of <loc reading="met">Pakistan</loc> on 14 August 1947, the Frontier Force Regiment was allocated to Pakistan and Bakhtiar Rana joined the newly established Pakistan Army and helped in its formation.
</sample>
<sample number="957">In September 2016 he criticised <loc reading="met">Wales</loc>' proposals that would partition the present Montgomeryshire UK Parliament constituency between three neighbouring seats, claiming it would "create a bureaucratic nightmare" of three MPs representing the existing shire county area.
</sample>
<sample number="958">The oil transport infrastructure in <loc reading="lit">Finland</loc> was built and is owned by Neste, and thus petrol stations usually obtain fuels from Neste, although the monopoly is no longer government-sanctioned.
</sample>
<sample number="959">They described Medvedev as the "brain" of the "KGB corporation" that rules <loc reading="met">Russia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="960">They were both passed by Germany, and <loc reading="met">Häggblad</loc> beat Hagen at the finish line for the bronze medal.
</sample>
<sample number="961">Southern bases on both coasts are used to organize infiltrations into <loc reading="lit">South Korea</loc> and Japan.
</sample>
<sample number="962">The Bearcamp River is a 26.3-mile-long (42.3 km) river at the southern edge of the <loc reading="lit">White Mountains</loc> in New Hampshire, the United States.
</sample>
<sample number="963">Most of the Masovian inheritance (except Czersk, who was already given to Konrad III as hereditary fief in 1495) was seriously threatened by the <loc reading="met">Kingdom of Poland</loc> at the time of Konrad III's death, and wasn't secured in his sons' hands until 14 March 1504, when by a ruling of King Alexander, the young princes received their whole patrimony as a fief.
</sample>
<sample number="964">She became the co-host of Qantas' in-flight entertainment programs in 2010 and was named the first Australian celebrity tourism ambassador for <loc reading="met">Chile</loc> in 2014.
</sample>
<sample number="965">Prior to the 1993 ban, <loc reading="met">China</loc> used tiger bone, which they believed to have healing powers, to yield tiger wine and traditional Chinese medicines .
</sample>
<sample number="966">She represented <loc reading="met">Greece</loc> in triathlon at the 2008 Summer Olympics.
</sample>
<sample number="967">Wuzhou or Wu Prefecture was a zhou (prefecture) in imperial <loc reading="lit">China</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="968">The Nagorno-Karabakh Autonomous Oblast voted to secede from Azerbaijan and join <loc reading="met">Armenia</loc>, triggering the Nagorno-Karabakh War.
</sample>
<sample number="969"><loc reading="met">Birmingham</loc> then escorted convoy WS-9A from the UK to South Africa arriving on 4 July 1941.
</sample>
<sample number="970"><loc reading="met">Britain</loc> requested Daoud's replacement because he has a reputation for corruption, ties to Afghanistan's Opium industry, and ties to the Taliban.
</sample>
<sample number="971">Israel has its own <loc reading="met">Afganistan</loc> which is Syria, and its own Iraq, which is Iran.
</sample>
<sample number="972">After immigrating to Canada in 1968, Costa continued his senior career playing for <loc reading="met">Toronto</loc> of the Canadian National Soccer League until 1984, becoming the longest serving player in the league and winning a championship with the club.
</sample>
<sample number="973">Hile is a village development committee in Baglung District in the Dhaulagiri Zone of central <loc reading="lit">Nepal</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="974">Before he was an astronaut, Casper was a United States Air Force fighter pilot, earning his pilot wings at Reese Air Force Base, <loc reading="lit">Texas</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="975">After visiting South America, Africa, and <loc reading="lit">India</loc>, Rhodes ended up in Australia, where he formed a partnership with a local company to acquire land in New Zealand.
</sample>
<sample number="976">In their first class of the day, Luke is introduced to Mike, Cat and Tank who were Peter's old friends and <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc>, the last person to move to Phoenix.
</sample>
<sample number="977">Hancock built gardens in the <loc reading="lit">UK</loc> in the 1920s, 30s and 40s and in the United States in the 1930s.
</sample>
<sample number="978">The communist radical group, the Red May, are trying to bring down <loc reading="met">Japan</loc>'s economy and take over the government.
</sample>
<sample number="979">In 1807 or 1808 he went to <loc reading="lit">England</loc> to study medicine at St Thomas' Hospital in London under Sir Astley Paston Cooper, a famous surgeon.
</sample>
<sample number="980"><loc reading="lit">France</loc> has unusual small municipalities.
</sample>
<sample number="981">In 1902 the ship was transferred to the navy of Colombia where it was armed with cannon and served in the Colombian navy as the gunboat <loc reading="met">Bogota</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="982"><loc reading="met">Japan</loc> has a long robotics history and high reputation in the robotics area.
</sample>
<sample number="983">He played at Stadion Brugglifeld for FC Aarau until 2002 when he headed to <loc reading="lit">Germany</loc> to play in the Bundesliga for Karlsruher SC.
</sample>
<sample number="984">Final incorporation of the region into Poland had nothing to do with the <loc reading="met">Vilnius</loc> issue - it was incorporated immediately as Lithuanian troops were pushed out of it (for the second time)in the summer of 1920.
</sample>
<sample number="985">Neste Corporation is an oil refining and marketing company located in <loc reading="lit">Espoo</loc>, Finland.
</sample>
<sample number="986">Ten days later, the <loc reading="met">United States</loc> designated Jabhat al-Nusra as a foreign terrorist organization, followed by the United Nations Security Council and many other countries.
</sample>
<sample number="987">The team has advanced to the second round in all of its appearances, in the process becoming the first team to score mercy rule wins over <loc reading="met">Cuba</loc> and the United States.
</sample>
<sample number="988">Shi Yu Quan has been appointed as new representative of <loc reading="met">China</loc> to the Mister International 2014 because the previous candidate, Daniel Che, was stripped of the title for "bad attitude".
</sample>
<sample number="989">He became an All Black in 1905, playing against <loc reading="met">Australia</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="990">In 1956 he was in the master class of Hans Leygraf, followed by concerts in Germany and tours of Western Europe, the U.S., <loc reading="lit">Israel</loc> and Japan.
</sample>
<sample number="991">Israel has its own Afganistan which is <loc reading="met">Syria</loc>, and its own Iraq, which is Iran.
</sample>
<sample number="992">Rushchinsky made his debut for USSR on 16 November 1924 in a friendly against <loc reading="met">Turkey</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="993">It is situated between French Guiana to the east and <loc reading="lit">Guyana</loc> to the west.
</sample>
<sample number="994"><loc reading="lit">Kunturiri</loc> is located in the La Paz Department, Los Andes Province, Pukarani Municipality, southeast of Chachakumani and northwest of Huayna Potosí.
</sample>
<sample number="995">Kraemer, a Lutheran with a dislike for Nazis, escaped Nazi Germany for <loc reading="lit">America</loc> in 1939, leaving behind his wife and son.
</sample>
<sample number="996">There were complaints of the way the dog's behavior was described and <loc reading="met">London</loc> followed up on the same theme with The Call of the Wild.
</sample>
<sample number="997">At that tournament, Spain defeated <loc reading="met">Zimbabwe</loc>, Philippines, Tonga and Japan to reach the finals, where it lost to Canada.
</sample>
<sample number="998">A wide release on the Plug Research label followed in the spring of 2006 and was supported with a European tour and a few shows around the <loc reading="lit">United States</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="999">They go to <loc reading="met">Jordan</loc>'s house and she discusses with them that she is pregnant.
</sample>
<sample number="1000">Ripley is a town on Lake Erie in the westernmost part of Chautauqua County, <loc reading="lit">New York</loc>, United States.
</sample>
<sample number="1001">Kaji Abhiman Singh Basnyat was chief of the army of the first unified <loc reading="met">Nepal</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="1002">Prior to Australian Federation the island of Tasmania was a colony of the British Empire, and as such was often at war with <loc reading="met">Britain</loc>’s enemies and European rivals, such as France and later Russia.
</sample>
<sample number="1003">The expressway ring road is a provincial-level road in <loc reading="lit">Beijing</loc> municipality.
</sample>
<sample number="1004">After O'Neill's release, he conspired with the king to bring the English army to <loc reading="lit">London</loc> against the radical Parliamentarians in what became known as the Second Army Plot, but the discovery of plot forced him to flee to the continent in mid-June 1641.
</sample>
<sample number="1005">Despite the <loc reading="met">Australia</loc> v England match later receiving Test status, and being the match that triggered the birth of The Ashes, the 1882 match is not considered to be part of The Ashes since it precedes the introduction of the trophy.
</sample>
<sample number="1006">The resolution was coauthored by <loc reading="met">France</loc> and the United States.
</sample>
<sample number="1007">Croatia was also a puppet state of <loc reading="met">Italy</loc> from 1941 to 1943.
</sample>
<sample number="1008">Optima is a <loc reading="lit">Miami</loc> -based real estate investment firm led by Chaim Schochet and 2/3rd owned by the Privat Group, one of Ukraine's largest business and banking groups.
</sample>
<sample number="1009">Yugoslavia won, ahead of Romania, <loc reading="met">Bulgaria</loc>, and Albania.
</sample>
<sample number="1010"><loc reading="met">Bogota</loc> shelled the city of Panama on November 3, 1903 during the secession of Panama from Colombia.
</sample>
<sample number="1011">Diplomatic missions were signed on October 18, 1979, between Nicaragua and the <loc reading="met">Soviet Union</loc> a few months after the Sandinista revolution.
</sample>
<sample number="1012">He had to leave Norway in 1941 due to the German occupation of Norway, and travelled via <loc reading="lit">Sweden</loc> to the United Kingdom, where he found work in the Ministry of Provisioning-in-exile.
</sample>
<sample number="1013">The Olympic torch relay was disrupted in London, Paris and San Francisco by protesters objecting to <loc reading="met">China</loc>'s human rights record.
</sample>
<sample number="1014">Fort Sainte Thérèse is the name given to three different forts built successively on one site, among a series of fortifications constructed during the 17th century by <loc reading="met">France</loc> along the Richelieu River, in the province of Quebec, in Montérégie.
</sample>
<sample number="1015">Its first head was also an American, and accountants were hired from <loc reading="lit">Lebanon</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="1016">In a 2016 ranking of Chinese high schools that send students to study in American universities, Shenzhen Foreign Language School ranked number 19 in mainland <loc reading="lit">China</loc> in terms of the number of students entering top American universities.
</sample>
<sample number="1017">He made his debut for <loc reading="met">Ireland</loc> against Australia in 1993 and was then selected for the 1994 ICC Trophy.
</sample>
<sample number="1018"><loc reading="met">Britain</loc> and Belarus established diplomatic relations in 1992 shortly after Belarus regained independence.
</sample>
<sample number="1019">In the 2013 World Baseball Classic, Puerto Rico became the second team from Western Hemisphere to advance to the final, eliminating two-time defending world champion <loc reading="met">Japan</loc> in the semifinals before finishing as the event's runners-up.
</sample>
<sample number="1020">With his increased oil revenues, and with his new vision of <loc reading="met">Iran</loc> as the hegemonic force in the region, a nuclear program became for Shah Pahlavi the symbol of progress and power.
</sample>
<sample number="1021">Ashrafiyat Sahnaya is a city in southern <loc reading="lit">Syria</loc>, administratively part of the Rif Dimashq Governorate, located southwest of Damascus.
</sample>
<sample number="1022">They were executed in both the <loc reading="lit">Marjeh Square</loc> in Damascus and Burj Square in Beirut.
</sample>
<sample number="1023">Balbo was the only leading Fascist to oppose both anti-Jewish racial laws and Mussolini's alliance with <loc reading="met">Nazi Germany</loc>.
</sample>
<sample number="1024">By 2007 its <loc reading="lit">New Zealand</loc> factory was weaving 950,000 square metres of various kinds of turf a year.
</sample>
<sample number="1025">His MA thesis was on <loc reading="met">South Africa</loc>'s post-apartheid transitional justice mechanisms and how some of those lessons could be applied to post-war Afghanistan.
</sample>
<sample number="1026">Mauro Badaracchi (born July 20, 1984 in Tivoli, <loc reading="lit">Rome</loc>) is an Italian sport shooter.
</sample>
</data>
